[
    {
        "academicYear": "2B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Facebook",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "vvsheth@uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Vishwa",
        "lastName": "Sheth",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer",
            "Product Designer",
            "Product Manager"
        ],
        "program": "Mechatronics Engineering",
        "question1": "Creating projects for helping improve lives is why I chose to be in engineering. Amongst all the different teams and groups I am able to join, Blueprint is one of the few that shares this goal with me. Bringing my shared passion to the team will not only help me achieve a dream I've had for years, but help make a real impact to others' lives. After all, it's not an understatement to say that now more than ever, humanity needs to learn to help itself. One of the many ways this can be done is through innovation and inspiration from those with the skills. This is exactly the opportunity Blueprint provides, which I'm more than eager to embark upon. I would also have the chance to be amongst like-minded peers that share a vision of the world, which would not only help me grow as a person, but make the projects that much more successful. All in all, I think Blueprint would help me start working towards the goals I've had for myself and also give me the chance to meet some amazing and inspiring people.",
        "question2": "My most recent contribution to a non-profit organization was in my twelfth grade when I was volunteering at a senior residence centre. I was in charge of recreational activities and organization, which meant I would organize anything from poker night to a small game of chess to a game of Wii tennis! I also spent one-on-one time with a lot of the residences simply catching up on their day and helping them with anything they needed. I volunteered at the residence for over a year and came to learn a lot of important skills such as communication with a variety of different people with different needs, organization of various activities that suit as many people as possible, and, most importantly, patience when it comes to tasks not going exactly as I planned.",
        "question3": "A project I'm most proud of also happens to be my most recent project, an Alexa skill that identifies who has arrived at your door and gives further prompts based on if it is a familiar face. This project was done with two of my friends, and involved a lot of different technologies. I took lead in organizing who was in charge of which task, which included writing the code for the Alexa skill itself, implementing the Microsoft Azure facial recognition API, and connecting both ends to a Firebase database for storing familiar faces. In terms of code difficulty, this project was not the most elaborate, but the reason why this has been my best project to date is because of the number of technologies we had to use and how well I was able to organize all of it together to make it work. We presented this at DeltaHacks V and, although we did not win, we definitely learned a lot in terms of project management and organization to make a working product.",
        "question4": "If you drill a hole into the Earth and into an orange with the same height, the remaining volume is exactly equal (Google the napkin ring problem)",
        "question5": "Not much here :)",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "Creating projects for helping improve lives is why I chose to be in engineering. Amongst all the different teams and groups I am able to join, Blueprint is one of the few that shares this goal with me. Bringing my shared passion to the team will not only help me achieve a dream I've had for years, but help make a real impact to others' lives. After all, it's not an understatement to say that now more than ever, humanity needs to learn to help itself. One of the many ways this can be done is through innovation and inspiration from those with the skills. This is exactly the opportunity Blueprint provides, which I'm more than eager to embark upon. I would also have the chance to be amongst like-minded peers that share a vision of the world, which would not only help me grow as a person, but make the projects that much more successful. All in all, I think Blueprint would help me start working towards the goals I've had for myself and also give me the chance to meet some amazing and inspiring people.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "My most recent contribution to a non-profit organization was in my twelfth grade when I was volunteering at a senior residence centre. I was in charge of recreational activities and organization, which meant I would organize anything from poker night to a small game of chess to a game of Wii tennis! I also spent one-on-one time with a lot of the residences simply catching up on their day and helping them with anything they needed. I volunteered at the residence for over a year and came to learn a lot of important skills such as communication with a variety of different people with different needs, organization of various activities that suit as many people as possible, and, most importantly, patience when it comes to tasks not going exactly as I planned.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "A project I'm most proud of also happens to be my most recent project, an Alexa skill that identifies who has arrived at your door and gives further prompts based on if it is a familiar face. This project was done with two of my friends, and involved a lot of different technologies. I took lead in organizing who was in charge of which task, which included writing the code for the Alexa skill itself, implementing the Microsoft Azure facial recognition API, and connecting both ends to a Firebase database for storing familiar faces. In terms of code difficulty, this project was not the most elaborate, but the reason why this has been my best project to date is because of the number of technologies we had to use and how well I was able to organize all of it together to make it work. We presented this at DeltaHacks V and, although we did not win, we definitely learned a lot in terms of project management and organization to make a working product.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "If you drill a hole into the Earth and into an orange with the same height, the remaining volume is exactly equal (Google the napkin ring problem)",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Not much here :)",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fd7a413bd-b398-777b-fa63-4d1abeca1540?alt=media&token=b6fc580c-f337-43a8-b8ce-7fdabb49a623",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fd7a413bd-b398-777b-fa63-4d1abeca1540?alt=media&token=b6fc580c-f337-43a8-b8ce-7fdabb49a623",
        "roleQuestion1": "When I first started programming, I decided to work on a large project which involved generating a 3D fractal mountain. In essence, the way this mountain is generated is by creating an initial triangle and splitting the first large triangle into multiple smaller triangles. I worked on this project in my eleventh grade and was oblivious to a lot of basic programming concepts such as recursion and classes. I was able to get around the different classes I made but splitting the triangle was something I just couldn't figure out. After banging my head for a week, I approached my high school computer science who introduced me to recursion. He taught me how I would be able to \"access\" each smaller triangle after the split and generate the rest of the mountain.",
        "roleQuestion2": "I created a basic portfolio website about myself (vishwasheth03.github.io) for anyone that wanted to look further into my past projects.\nUnfortunately I haven't had time to update the website to my most recent accomplishments but I think it was a good way of demonstrating my skills more in depth!",
        "roleQuestion3": "Seemingly trivial but still very annoying, on the SkipTheDishes app, there is no way for you to message your driver while they are delivering. There is also no way of checking their profile and requesting to change the driver. Perhaps the latter is a more risky feature to implement, but at least contacting the driver is important in case you need to give them additional information or an emergency comes up! One may argue that messaging your driver while they are driving is dangerous because it prompts them to check their phone. To avoid this the app can simply implement a feature that locks the messages while they are in motion, but at least they would be able to see the message when they’ve come to a stop.",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Product Designer": "I created a basic portfolio website about myself (vishwasheth03.github.io) for anyone that wanted to look further into my past projects.\nUnfortunately I haven't had time to update the website to my most recent accomplishments but I think it was a good way of demonstrating my skills more in depth!",
            "Product Manager": "Seemingly trivial but still very annoying, on the SkipTheDishes app, there is no way for you to message your driver while they are delivering. There is also no way of checking their profile and requesting to change the driver. Perhaps the latter is a more risky feature to implement, but at least contacting the driver is important in case you need to give them additional information or an emergency comes up! One may argue that messaging your driver while they are driving is dangerous because it prompts them to check their phone. To avoid this the app can simply implement a feature that locks the messages while they are in motion, but at least they would be able to see the message when they’ve come to a stop.",
            "Project Developer": "When I first started programming, I decided to work on a large project which involved generating a 3D fractal mountain. In essence, the way this mountain is generated is by creating an initial triangle and splitting the first large triangle into multiple smaller triangles. I worked on this project in my eleventh grade and was oblivious to a lot of basic programming concepts such as recursion and classes. I was able to get around the different classes I made but splitting the triangle was something I just couldn't figure out. After banging my head for a week, I approached my high school computer science who introduced me to recursion. He taught me how I would be able to \"access\" each smaller triangle after the split and generate the rest of the mountain."
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551109692334
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "2B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Word of mouth",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "k4singha@edu.uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Kritin",
        "lastName": "Singhal",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer",
            "Project Lead"
        ],
        "program": "Computer Science",
        "question1": "The industry is slowly moving from good brains to good hearts. I am excited about meeting talented people at Blueprint. But more than that, I am extremely passionate about the idea of contributing towards non-profits through the power of technology.",
        "question2": "During summer 2016, I visited the country of Bhutan to start a community campaign to foster more inclusiveness in the society. Bhutan was raged by disability discrimination which was reflected even at young children going to school. In our campaign, we visited plenty of schools around the capital, hosted workshops among the students and motivated the disabled ones to take up pride and follow their goals. It was a month full of workshops and speeches, collaborated with Disabled Persons' Association of Bhutan that aids blind people in and around the capital. ",
        "question3": "I recently worked on a project that helps university students to conquer mental health. The name of the project is Nova, which is essentially an Artificial Intelligence chatbot that acts as an unbiased, and non-judgemental friend to any student who needs a person to talk to, anytime of the day. Nova also has the ability to detect emergency situations through Natural Language Processing and can inform the authorities, if needs be. We won the best Hackathon project and we also were qualified in the Velocity Fund Finals 5k.",
        "question4": "I can play four instruments",
        "question5": "Portfolio: www.kritinsinghal.com",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "The industry is slowly moving from good brains to good hearts. I am excited about meeting talented people at Blueprint. But more than that, I am extremely passionate about the idea of contributing towards non-profits through the power of technology.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "During summer 2016, I visited the country of Bhutan to start a community campaign to foster more inclusiveness in the society. Bhutan was raged by disability discrimination which was reflected even at young children going to school. In our campaign, we visited plenty of schools around the capital, hosted workshops among the students and motivated the disabled ones to take up pride and follow their goals. It was a month full of workshops and speeches, collaborated with Disabled Persons' Association of Bhutan that aids blind people in and around the capital. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I recently worked on a project that helps university students to conquer mental health. The name of the project is Nova, which is essentially an Artificial Intelligence chatbot that acts as an unbiased, and non-judgemental friend to any student who needs a person to talk to, anytime of the day. Nova also has the ability to detect emergency situations through Natural Language Processing and can inform the authorities, if needs be. We won the best Hackathon project and we also were qualified in the Velocity Fund Finals 5k.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I can play four instruments",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Portfolio: www.kritinsinghal.com",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\resume (3).pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F606575f1-f889-846a-538f-6736baa20f11?alt=media&token=6d515d40-f74b-450e-88d7-7325dc640f9e",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F606575f1-f889-846a-538f-6736baa20f11?alt=media&token=6d515d40-f74b-450e-88d7-7325dc640f9e",
        "roleQuestion1": "In my most recent coop, I was a given a project to automate snapshot testing for the website by building a web-scraping bot. The biggest issue was to handle logins for the pages that required it. Initially, I tried saving the cookie and hitting the authentication API. This method, though successful, processed really slowly and made the whole testing inefficient. Later, I came up with a new login method, which I named Snake. Snake is essentially a python program that generates random token and session numbers for login and instead of making an intercept request with the credentials, it uses those tokens to make the requests. This method was way faster as it processed 4 times faster than the usual credential authentication method.  ",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "In my most recent coop, I was a given a project to automate snapshot testing for the website by building a web-scraping bot. The biggest issue was to handle logins for the pages that required it. Initially, I tried saving the cookie and hitting the authentication API. This method, though successful, processed really slowly and made the whole testing inefficient. Later, I came up with a new login method, which I named Snake. Snake is essentially a python program that generates random token and session numbers for login and instead of making an intercept request with the credentials, it uses those tokens to make the requests. This method was way faster as it processed 4 times faster than the usual credential authentication method.  "
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551111061254
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "1A",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Facebook",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "h34cai@edu.uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Huichuan ",
        "lastName": "Cai",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer"
        ],
        "program": "Computer engineering ",
        "question1": "I want to meet awesome people and do some project that is nonprofitable and contribute myself. \npractice coding skills as well as teamwork skills before coop",
        "question2": "BASE news writing team in Renison: writing article for more than 100 people weekly",
        "question3": "I learned programming totally by myself, and I am constructing Portfolio website with the instruction on Youtube.",
        "question4": "I am eager to help people and am willing to learn new things",
        "question5": "I don't have class in the spring term but I really want to help in this club so I can \ncontribute 20 hours a week for this club. I can learn all the technical or non-technical things with passion.",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I want to meet awesome people and do some project that is nonprofitable and contribute myself. \npractice coding skills as well as teamwork skills before coop",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "BASE news writing team in Renison: writing article for more than 100 people weekly",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I learned programming totally by myself, and I am constructing Portfolio website with the instruction on Youtube.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I am eager to help people and am willing to learn new things",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I don't have class in the spring term but I really want to help in this club so I can \ncontribute 20 hours a week for this club. I can learn all the technical or non-technical things with passion.",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\real_resume.doc",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F73bde1ca-8416-2108-6b39-fcffe092ead0?alt=media&token=579bd3a4-ce91-4bc9-8944-8156338a9510",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F73bde1ca-8416-2108-6b39-fcffe092ead0?alt=media&token=579bd3a4-ce91-4bc9-8944-8156338a9510",
        "roleQuestion1": "I learned to build something mainly by following the tutorial. Sometimes problems happened and I have exactly same code with tutorial, after I searched on Google or Stack overflow, sometimes I still cannot solve it.\nI will attend some club activities(UWcoffeeNcode) and ask upper year students.",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "I learned to build something mainly by following the tutorial. Sometimes problems happened and I have exactly same code with tutorial, after I searched on Google or Stack overflow, sometimes I still cannot solve it.\nI will attend some club activities(UWcoffeeNcode) and ask upper year students."
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551148917210
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "2B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Facebook",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "s2koul@edu.uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "SNEH",
        "lastName": "KOUL",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer"
        ],
        "program": "Computer Engineering ",
        "question1": "Since a few months ,I have been thinking to myself that I am so privileged to study at UW ,intern in such good companies ,have a good health and such amazing family and friends. I would really love to help  those who are not as privileged as me . I saw Blueprint as a great opportunity to help others because I love coding and I want to help others and something which could combine both is an ideal place for me to be",
        "question2": " I have worked with Elixir labs as a Software developer on their End Slavery Now project https://www.endslaverynow.org/ to make the WebApp and helped in the backend as well .Back in India I have worked with TeachIndia to teach the janitors of our school to communicate in English and about Girl Education and equality which is a major issue back in my country .I have worked in communal harmony movement to promote all religions and communities ",
        "question3": "Led the team of three to develop a backend from scratch for the SheLeads\ngame which is a women empowerment startup .The startup won a 25K pitch competition because of the successful delivery of the project in the market",
        "question4": "I am good at poetry being an engineer <:",
        "question5": "",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "Since a few months ,I have been thinking to myself that I am so privileged to study at UW ,intern in such good companies ,have a good health and such amazing family and friends. I would really love to help  those who are not as privileged as me . I saw Blueprint as a great opportunity to help others because I love coding and I want to help others and something which could combine both is an ideal place for me to be",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": " I have worked with Elixir labs as a Software developer on their End Slavery Now project https://www.endslaverynow.org/ to make the WebApp and helped in the backend as well .Back in India I have worked with TeachIndia to teach the janitors of our school to communicate in English and about Girl Education and equality which is a major issue back in my country .I have worked in communal harmony movement to promote all religions and communities ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Led the team of three to develop a backend from scratch for the SheLeads\ngame which is a women empowerment startup .The startup won a 25K pitch competition because of the successful delivery of the project in the market",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I am good at poetry being an engineer <:",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\Resume1.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F085963f0-d1a6-622e-3355-716ce02881bb?alt=media&token=0804beec-cbbe-4052-98e7-756dc7bd5e92",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F085963f0-d1a6-622e-3355-716ce02881bb?alt=media&token=0804beec-cbbe-4052-98e7-756dc7bd5e92",
        "roleQuestion1": "Well one challenge we faced is building an authentication system to login or signup in the game for SheLeads .We were building an authentication system for girls of 5-6 years old who dont have email or phone and cant remember password also ,Could write upper case or lower case or mix of both  or any strange things .So I came up with this https://sheleadsgame.com/login/ and ensured that all edge cases were checked according to how a young girl could behave . Project became a success at the end !",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "Well one challenge we faced is building an authentication system to login or signup in the game for SheLeads .We were building an authentication system for girls of 5-6 years old who dont have email or phone and cant remember password also ,Could write upper case or lower case or mix of both  or any strange things .So I came up with this https://sheleadsgame.com/login/ and ensured that all edge cases were checked according to how a young girl could behave . Project became a success at the end !"
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551151382023
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "2B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Facebook",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "j7gupta@edu.uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Jaya",
        "lastName": "Gupta",
        "positions": [
            "Product Manager",
            "VP External",
            "Content Director"
        ],
        "program": "Nanotechnology Engineering",
        "question1": "I want to contribute to non-profits in a meaningful way and meet like-minded people. I love volunteering; I have volunteered for various non-profits in the past and have gotten involved with a number of them in a leadership role. I'm passionate about social entrepreneurship and technology, which is why I love the work UW Blueprint is doing and want to get involved. ",
        "question2": "I've volunteered for community organizations such as Goodwill, The Salvation Army, The Heart and Stroke Foundation, the TD Foundation for the Environment, the Hindu Cultural Centre in London, ON, and the Breast Cancer Society of Canada mainly as an organizing volunteer. I have contributed to school organizations such as Canadian Cancer Society Relay for Life fundraisers, The Salvation Army SCROOGE can drives, and the student-run non-profit, Green Initiative Canada (GIC), through leadership roles primarily in marketing (social media and design of promotional materials). I also had the opportunity to be a Director for GIC and spearhead the organization's first chapter in my hometown of London, ON, which involved recruiting an executive team of students and organizing events in the London area to raise environmental awareness among youth. ",
        "question3": "I'm most passionate about the work I've done for the UW BioTEC conference. BioTEC is Canada's top student-run biotech conference. I've helped to increase BioTEC's online presence by managing our social media strategy, allowing us to reach our applicant/social media metric goals and reach more students which led to a better event overall. I'm currently building on that success by reaching out to external groups at other universities to form partnerships that will help BioTEC in the future. ",
        "question4": "I used to swim competitively. ",
        "question5": "I genuinely believe in the work Blueprint does to help non-profits, and have even referred some NPOs to consider applying to UW Blueprint for tech-related projects. ",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I want to contribute to non-profits in a meaningful way and meet like-minded people. I love volunteering; I have volunteered for various non-profits in the past and have gotten involved with a number of them in a leadership role. I'm passionate about social entrepreneurship and technology, which is why I love the work UW Blueprint is doing and want to get involved. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I've volunteered for community organizations such as Goodwill, The Salvation Army, The Heart and Stroke Foundation, the TD Foundation for the Environment, the Hindu Cultural Centre in London, ON, and the Breast Cancer Society of Canada mainly as an organizing volunteer. I have contributed to school organizations such as Canadian Cancer Society Relay for Life fundraisers, The Salvation Army SCROOGE can drives, and the student-run non-profit, Green Initiative Canada (GIC), through leadership roles primarily in marketing (social media and design of promotional materials). I also had the opportunity to be a Director for GIC and spearhead the organization's first chapter in my hometown of London, ON, which involved recruiting an executive team of students and organizing events in the London area to raise environmental awareness among youth. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I'm most passionate about the work I've done for the UW BioTEC conference. BioTEC is Canada's top student-run biotech conference. I've helped to increase BioTEC's online presence by managing our social media strategy, allowing us to reach our applicant/social media metric goals and reach more students which led to a better event overall. I'm currently building on that success by reaching out to external groups at other universities to form partnerships that will help BioTEC in the future. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I used to swim competitively. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I genuinely believe in the work Blueprint does to help non-profits, and have even referred some NPOs to consider applying to UW Blueprint for tech-related projects. ",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\Jaya Gupta Resume - UW Blueprint.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fa6395faa-84f1-5212-9907-c7fce49ff153?alt=media&token=04a142f1-4239-431c-88cf-ed1efd5214b7",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fa6395faa-84f1-5212-9907-c7fce49ff153?alt=media&token=04a142f1-4239-431c-88cf-ed1efd5214b7",
        "roleQuestion1": "I dislike my S'well water bottle because it's opaque so I always have to open it to see what the water level is inside. I'd change this by making the whole bottle transparent or adding a thin, transparent line along the side that will let me see the water level. ",
        "roleQuestion2": "The non-profit must be credible and in need of Blueprint's services with no other reasonable means of completing the project. Their project must involve technology to fit Blueprint's expertise, have substantial community impact that can be measured, and be time-feasible. ",
        "roleQuestion3": "A powerful brand can conjure the right image in consumers' minds simply when they see the organization's logo or hear their name. It can communicate the brand's core values and serves as a symbol of high-quality and credibility to consumers. ",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Content Director": "A powerful brand can conjure the right image in consumers' minds simply when they see the organization's logo or hear their name. It can communicate the brand's core values and serves as a symbol of high-quality and credibility to consumers. ",
            "Product Manager": "I dislike my S'well water bottle because it's opaque so I always have to open it to see what the water level is inside. I'd change this by making the whole bottle transparent or adding a thin, transparent line along the side that will let me see the water level. ",
            "VP External": "The non-profit must be credible and in need of Blueprint's services with no other reasonable means of completing the project. Their project must involve technology to fit Blueprint's expertise, have substantial community impact that can be measured, and be time-feasible. "
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551151742966
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "3A",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Co-op",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Co-op"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Word of mouth",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "azdanowi@edu.uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Alex",
        "lastName": "Zdanowicz",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer"
        ],
        "program": "Computer Science",
        "question1": "I love programming, I love working with people, and above all else I love helping people, so doing all three at once is a no-brainer.",
        "question2": "I've donated blood the American Red Cross, I oftentimes help my friends with understanding concepts in class, generally trying to be a helpful person from day-to-day",
        "question3": "A little crypto-currency application that grabs the prices of different crypto currencies from different websites' APIs and displays them in one coherent place in the application: https://github.com/Zandwhich/CryptoCurrencyPrices . (Please note that I went a little over-the-top in the abstraction/interface usage in this project. This was primarily to reinforce principles in class. I would not go this crazy when working on a project shared by a larger group, as it makes it hard to understand and follow.)",
        "question4": "I speak two languages fluently, and am learning my third.",
        "question5": "I am going to be on a co-op term this coming term, but don't know exactly where I'll be (rankings come out this Friday). I selected \"Yes\" for the question \"Are you going to be in Waterloo\", because If I am in Waterloo, I would be interested in working for Blueprint. If I am not in Waterloo, I would probably apply for a coming term.",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I love programming, I love working with people, and above all else I love helping people, so doing all three at once is a no-brainer.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I've donated blood the American Red Cross, I oftentimes help my friends with understanding concepts in class, generally trying to be a helpful person from day-to-day",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "A little crypto-currency application that grabs the prices of different crypto currencies from different websites' APIs and displays them in one coherent place in the application: https://github.com/Zandwhich/CryptoCurrencyPrices . (Please note that I went a little over-the-top in the abstraction/interface usage in this project. This was primarily to reinforce principles in class. I would not go this crazy when working on a project shared by a larger group, as it makes it hard to understand and follow.)",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I speak two languages fluently, and am learning my third.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I am going to be on a co-op term this coming term, but don't know exactly where I'll be (rankings come out this Friday). I selected \"Yes\" for the question \"Are you going to be in Waterloo\", because If I am in Waterloo, I would be interested in working for Blueprint. If I am not in Waterloo, I would probably apply for a coming term.",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\Alexander Zdanowicz - Resume 8.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fa38d12dd-ae69-04c3-2124-4ac663f4c941?alt=media&token=853b42c0-b393-4808-9f6b-13634c1005d9",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fa38d12dd-ae69-04c3-2124-4ac663f4c941?alt=media&token=853b42c0-b393-4808-9f6b-13634c1005d9",
        "roleQuestion1": "When working on my application that I listed above, a recurring challenge that I faced was \"how do I use this specific library to create the UI I want?\" For example, when I wanted to create a table, I didn't originally know how to do that, but I knew that Java had to have some sort of built-in table in its Swing framework (which I am using). So I Googled around and found some results on how to use the JTable, and then started applying that to my project. It's these little challenges put together (how do I make this work in the UI?, etc.) where I constantly push my knowledge of the language and the frameworks/libraries to the limit, and learn new technologies.",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "When working on my application that I listed above, a recurring challenge that I faced was \"how do I use this specific library to create the UI I want?\" For example, when I wanted to create a table, I didn't originally know how to do that, but I knew that Java had to have some sort of built-in table in its Swing framework (which I am using). So I Googled around and found some results on how to use the JTable, and then started applying that to my project. It's these little challenges put together (how do I make this work in the UI?, etc.) where I constantly push my knowledge of the language and the frameworks/libraries to the limit, and learn new technologies."
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551217517159
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "1B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Word of mouth",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "akshah@uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Amay",
        "lastName": "Shah",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer",
            "Product Manager"
        ],
        "program": "Systems Design Engineering ",
        "question1": "Blueprint gives students a win-win situation by helping them give back to society while allowing them to learn how to collaborate with others and master skills which will help them in their co-ops and in future projects. ",
        "question2": "YuvaUnstoppable, AngelXpress, Helping Bands ",
        "question3": "I worked on a project with YuvaUnstoppable to implement digital education across the rural sectors of India and helped teachers understand and use this technology. ",
        "question4": "I remember the lyrics to every single Maroon 5 song. ",
        "question5": "",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "Blueprint gives students a win-win situation by helping them give back to society while allowing them to learn how to collaborate with others and master skills which will help them in their co-ops and in future projects. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "YuvaUnstoppable, AngelXpress, Helping Bands ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I worked on a project with YuvaUnstoppable to implement digital education across the rural sectors of India and helped teachers understand and use this technology. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I remember the lyrics to every single Maroon 5 song. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\1B ME .pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F1e40b436-f5c6-8796-c1ed-0402ed990da2?alt=media&token=db281529-f45b-47a5-8cd0-d04333d2658f",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F1e40b436-f5c6-8796-c1ed-0402ed990da2?alt=media&token=db281529-f45b-47a5-8cd0-d04333d2658f",
        "roleQuestion1": "I dislike the current iPhone (despite getting it) because of its single charging and earphone port. The product was created this way in the hope to make it slimmer, which it did. However, it led to the phone getting hotter quicker and decreasing its accessibility as you can't listen to music when charging or vice versa, something essential to a majority of the teenage and young adult population, a major segment of Apple's target audience. I would change it by incorporating the old earphone port which allows this phone to connect to regular earphones as well, while also enabling people to charge and listen to music at the same time. If they want to decrease the width, they can do it by other methods. However, the change in width is too minimal in exchange for these problems.",
        "roleQuestion2": "A technical challenge I overcame was on my co-op when I had to write multiple similar functions as part of the different applications the company had. However, I came up with the idea to use azure functions as I knew the company had an account and this streamlined the entire process. We further went ahead and created a dashboard as this company had a lot of data and used Azure power analytics and BI. Hence, I solved the problem of writing repetitive code through the use of azure. ",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Product Manager": "I dislike the current iPhone (despite getting it) because of its single charging and earphone port. The product was created this way in the hope to make it slimmer, which it did. However, it led to the phone getting hotter quicker and decreasing its accessibility as you can't listen to music when charging or vice versa, something essential to a majority of the teenage and young adult population, a major segment of Apple's target audience. I would change it by incorporating the old earphone port which allows this phone to connect to regular earphones as well, while also enabling people to charge and listen to music at the same time. If they want to decrease the width, they can do it by other methods. However, the change in width is too minimal in exchange for these problems.",
            "Project Developer": "A technical challenge I overcame was on my co-op when I had to write multiple similar functions as part of the different applications the company had. However, I came up with the idea to use azure functions as I knew the company had an account and this streamlined the entire process. We further went ahead and created a dashboard as this company had a lot of data and used Azure power analytics and BI. Hence, I solved the problem of writing repetitive code through the use of azure. "
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551239307763
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "3A",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Co-op",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Co-op"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Word of mouth",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "nt2phan@uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Nina",
        "lastName": "Phan",
        "positions": [
            "Product Designer"
        ],
        "program": "Biomedical Engineering",
        "question1": "I want to join Blueprint for the opportunity to not only make a big impact for non-profit organizations (NPOs), but also to creatively express the ideas of the team at a high level. I believe that in designing for NPOs, there is more potential impact as we are designing for underserved users, but more unknowns. Being in biomedical engineering has exposed me to complex human centric problems. Every problem I’ve encountered has been unique and multifaceted in terms of user research and ideation. Last co-op, I took my experience in designing for accessibility to reshape the UX at Ontario Teachers’ Pension Plan. It was here that I realized the importance of intergenerational design due to the great age range we were designing for. I believe that as designers, to make real impact, innovation has to be based around everyone— because talking about difference creates and continues a needless divide.  I hope to take my experience of inclusive design and contribute to the huge positive impact Blueprint has made for NPOs. I would love to work with people with diverse perspectives because more often than not, it takes several unique pair of eyes to drive impactful and brilliant design.",
        "question2": "During high school, I have made contributions to the Terry Fox Foundation, the Eliminate Project and Doctors without Borders. I was the president of my town’s Terry Fox Club. My responsibilities included organizing meetings with my executive team, planning and overseeing fundraising events, communicating with speakers of the foundation to organize an assembly for the student population, planning the annual Terry Fox Run and reaching out to local businesses for donations toward a barbecue for the run. We raised $6000 that year within a 2-week period. The Eliminate Project aims to raise money for vaccination against maternal and neonatal tetanus in third world countries. I organized our town’s annual spaghetti dinner. This involved reaching out to grocery stores for donations, organizing kitchen, silent auction, set-up/clean-up and ticket sales teams, as well as designing posters and tickets. The dinner raised $1400. Having been part of the Social Justice Club in high school, I organized a teacher karaoke event, where students had to work together to hit the monetary threshold to see the teacher of their choice sing. The event raised $500 for Doctors without Borders to provide aid to Syrian refugees. ",
        "question3": "At Ontario Teachers’ Pension Plan, I was responsible for designing the user experience for survivors, who are the loved ones of deceased members of the pension plan. This project involved user research, user journey mapping, personas, wireframing to design a microsite for survivors where they could register and be directed back to the member website to sign in and their personalized dashboard. The microsite involved designing for accessibility and creating empathetic copywrite for these users who have recently lost their loved ones. The dashboard design taught me inclusive design, as this was the touchpoint where the survivor experience was integrated with the member experience and the dashboard had to have consistency across users. I mapped out user journeys and created personas, which allowed me to understand the common goals that each user would have for the dashboard. The project holds a lot of impact in allowing survivors to self-service and avoid having to talk to someone during their period of grief. This is the project that I am most proud of. I decreased the number of touch-points for survivors to accomplish mandatory tasks, and in turn, increased the time efficiency of the call centre. ",
        "question4": "Last term, I traded in my crocs for Heelys, and I have gotten quite good at Heely-ing. ",
        "question5": "I used to play a lot of basketball back in high school and would love to play sometime with the club homies. \n\nP.S. I think the Bucks will lose to the Raptors in 7 in the eastern conference finals. \n",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I want to join Blueprint for the opportunity to not only make a big impact for non-profit organizations (NPOs), but also to creatively express the ideas of the team at a high level. I believe that in designing for NPOs, there is more potential impact as we are designing for underserved users, but more unknowns. Being in biomedical engineering has exposed me to complex human centric problems. Every problem I’ve encountered has been unique and multifaceted in terms of user research and ideation. Last co-op, I took my experience in designing for accessibility to reshape the UX at Ontario Teachers’ Pension Plan. It was here that I realized the importance of intergenerational design due to the great age range we were designing for. I believe that as designers, to make real impact, innovation has to be based around everyone— because talking about difference creates and continues a needless divide.  I hope to take my experience of inclusive design and contribute to the huge positive impact Blueprint has made for NPOs. I would love to work with people with diverse perspectives because more often than not, it takes several unique pair of eyes to drive impactful and brilliant design.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "During high school, I have made contributions to the Terry Fox Foundation, the Eliminate Project and Doctors without Borders. I was the president of my town’s Terry Fox Club. My responsibilities included organizing meetings with my executive team, planning and overseeing fundraising events, communicating with speakers of the foundation to organize an assembly for the student population, planning the annual Terry Fox Run and reaching out to local businesses for donations toward a barbecue for the run. We raised $6000 that year within a 2-week period. The Eliminate Project aims to raise money for vaccination against maternal and neonatal tetanus in third world countries. I organized our town’s annual spaghetti dinner. This involved reaching out to grocery stores for donations, organizing kitchen, silent auction, set-up/clean-up and ticket sales teams, as well as designing posters and tickets. The dinner raised $1400. Having been part of the Social Justice Club in high school, I organized a teacher karaoke event, where students had to work together to hit the monetary threshold to see the teacher of their choice sing. The event raised $500 for Doctors without Borders to provide aid to Syrian refugees. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "At Ontario Teachers’ Pension Plan, I was responsible for designing the user experience for survivors, who are the loved ones of deceased members of the pension plan. This project involved user research, user journey mapping, personas, wireframing to design a microsite for survivors where they could register and be directed back to the member website to sign in and their personalized dashboard. The microsite involved designing for accessibility and creating empathetic copywrite for these users who have recently lost their loved ones. The dashboard design taught me inclusive design, as this was the touchpoint where the survivor experience was integrated with the member experience and the dashboard had to have consistency across users. I mapped out user journeys and created personas, which allowed me to understand the common goals that each user would have for the dashboard. The project holds a lot of impact in allowing survivors to self-service and avoid having to talk to someone during their period of grief. This is the project that I am most proud of. I decreased the number of touch-points for survivors to accomplish mandatory tasks, and in turn, increased the time efficiency of the call centre. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Last term, I traded in my crocs for Heelys, and I have gotten quite good at Heely-ing. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I used to play a lot of basketball back in high school and would love to play sometime with the club homies. \n\nP.S. I think the Bucks will lose to the Raptors in 7 in the eastern conference finals. \n",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\resume - Nina Phan 2019.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F24515a2e-508c-c151-02f0-8f0627430904?alt=media&token=20123056-e63a-4ff0-8afb-7edc6e82c925",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F24515a2e-508c-c151-02f0-8f0627430904?alt=media&token=20123056-e63a-4ff0-8afb-7edc6e82c925",
        "roleQuestion1": "",
        "roleQuestion2": "www.nphn.squarespace.com\nPassword: Jackfruit111\n",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Product Designer": "www.nphn.squarespace.com\nPassword: Jackfruit111\n"
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551246060092
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "2B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Word of mouth",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "austin.jiang@uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Austin",
        "lastName": "Jiang",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer"
        ],
        "program": "Software Engineering",
        "question1": "Currently in co-op and most likely the rest of my career, I'll be working in a tech culture driven by profit and I kind of feel like I've sold my soul to corporate America. Thus, I feel that Blueprint is a great opportunity to re-balance my lifestyle, work for companies whose mottos I can truly find myself aligned with. Companies focused on improving the dire conditions of the environment, or the situations oompanies driven by a desire to improve the world, and not a desire to ship product to market as soon as possible. Technology can have a startling impact on our ability to create change, and I'd like to help the effort. ",
        "question2": "In high school, I was a regular volunteer for large events in my home town - Markham (Night It Up, Ribfest, etc) - all events hosted by local non-profit organizations. Moreover, I also volunteered for 10, 000 Trees and other non-profits geared towards planting trees in the area.  ",
        "question3": "At QHacks, my team created a SMS-based app designed to help help people who need food or a place to stay. Tons of food goes to waste every day (leftovers from bakeries, grocery stores, etc.) and helps them get in contact with people who could use it. Texting the number gave you a listing of people offering food / shelter and directions from your current address to your destination. It was built to be entirely SMS-based to account for the fact that people who might need this service might not always have data/wifi access. Though it was quite simple in scope, it felt good to build something that could have a positive impact on people in need for once. ",
        "question4": "I've watched over 30 movies so far in 2019! My favorite has been 'The Handmaiden' (2016). ",
        "question5": "Save the bees",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "Currently in co-op and most likely the rest of my career, I'll be working in a tech culture driven by profit and I kind of feel like I've sold my soul to corporate America. Thus, I feel that Blueprint is a great opportunity to re-balance my lifestyle, work for companies whose mottos I can truly find myself aligned with. Companies focused on improving the dire conditions of the environment, or the situations oompanies driven by a desire to improve the world, and not a desire to ship product to market as soon as possible. Technology can have a startling impact on our ability to create change, and I'd like to help the effort. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "In high school, I was a regular volunteer for large events in my home town - Markham (Night It Up, Ribfest, etc) - all events hosted by local non-profit organizations. Moreover, I also volunteered for 10, 000 Trees and other non-profits geared towards planting trees in the area.  ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "At QHacks, my team created a SMS-based app designed to help help people who need food or a place to stay. Tons of food goes to waste every day (leftovers from bakeries, grocery stores, etc.) and helps them get in contact with people who could use it. Texting the number gave you a listing of people offering food / shelter and directions from your current address to your destination. It was built to be entirely SMS-based to account for the fact that people who might need this service might not always have data/wifi access. Though it was quite simple in scope, it felt good to build something that could have a positive impact on people in need for once. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I've watched over 30 movies so far in 2019! My favorite has been 'The Handmaiden' (2016). ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Save the bees",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\resumev2.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F5ad941b7-f093-4792-bb22-614f15a7de81?alt=media&token=0cd0eac3-f64a-4be5-afdc-698cb1df5964",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F5ad941b7-f093-4792-bb22-614f15a7de81?alt=media&token=0cd0eac3-f64a-4be5-afdc-698cb1df5964",
        "roleQuestion1": "At work, a priority has been to reduce EC2 costs and the team wanted to explore if any CI jobs could be executed on Lambda. The job I picked was executed in a docker container, and it didn't make any sense to me how it could be executed in a server-less style and had me stuck for a good week. One day, one of my co-workers off-handedly asked 'why don't you just run the docker container on Lambda'. I had never thought to even try it because I'd never heard of this approach, and containers are usually associated with EC2 or ECS, but never Lambda. It turns out, last year researchers from Spain published a framework in a small academic journal designed exactly for this purpose. An obscure paper solved all my problems! Try anything, you'll never know what actually will work.",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "At work, a priority has been to reduce EC2 costs and the team wanted to explore if any CI jobs could be executed on Lambda. The job I picked was executed in a docker container, and it didn't make any sense to me how it could be executed in a server-less style and had me stuck for a good week. One day, one of my co-workers off-handedly asked 'why don't you just run the docker container on Lambda'. I had never thought to even try it because I'd never heard of this approach, and containers are usually associated with EC2 or ECS, but never Lambda. It turns out, last year researchers from Spain published a framework in a small academic journal designed exactly for this purpose. An obscure paper solved all my problems! Try anything, you'll never know what actually will work."
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551254728525
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "2B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Word of mouth",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "graciexia@gmail.com",
        "firstName": "Gracie",
        "lastName": "Xia",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer",
            "Product Designer",
            "Content Director"
        ],
        "program": "Software Engineering",
        "question1": "In high school, I was always involved in volunteer work and events that helped people. Whether that was giving physical help, helping to build others confidence or just offering resource and support, it was something I enjoyed thoroughly. After I entered university, I think I lost that part of myself. I was frustrated by the fact that, the skills I was learning could only contribute to monetary value and or self gain. But that’s simply not true. I learned about you guys and even though the form of help you are giving is different from conventional volunteer work, it’s actually really important to help non-for-profit organizations adapt to the technical space and help make their platform more easily accessible to the rest of the world. So, I guess I want to join Blueprint for its purpose, using the skills I have to help others.\n",
        "question2": "In high school, I volunteered at my local YMCA as a child camp leader and I also participated in a lot of youth leadership conferences as a mentor. In addition, I also had the chance to be a part of our city’s multicultural youth council which focused on hosting events, workshops and conferences relating to the different cultures within our city, the culture of our own city and creating a space for youth to talk and discuss anything they wanted regarding their identity and culture. In university I worked as a organizer for Hack the North, but other than that I stopped actively participating within my community and doing pure volunteer work, which I really want to get back into.",
        "question3": "Last year I was a designer/illustrator for Hack the North and I had the awesome opportunity to help rebuild and rebrand Hack the North with 4 other really cool designers. We developed everything including the typography, color usage, illustrations, the Hack the North homepage, online/mobile application experience, posters, apparel and swag items within a span of ​six months​. I’ve never worked on such a long term design project with such motivated people and I’m really proud of the fact that they gave me the trust to help build it.",
        "question4": "I’m currently working on putting animations over the “Gonna Get Over You” music video by Sara Bareilles for fun. So far, I’ve produced a lot of neat gifs :) I’ll be happy to show them to you all!",
        "question5": "I can do both design and development as well as basic animation. I’m very comfortable designing, however I would like to improve my programming abilities and gain more confidence in that area!",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "In high school, I was always involved in volunteer work and events that helped people. Whether that was giving physical help, helping to build others confidence or just offering resource and support, it was something I enjoyed thoroughly. After I entered university, I think I lost that part of myself. I was frustrated by the fact that, the skills I was learning could only contribute to monetary value and or self gain. But that’s simply not true. I learned about you guys and even though the form of help you are giving is different from conventional volunteer work, it’s actually really important to help non-for-profit organizations adapt to the technical space and help make their platform more easily accessible to the rest of the world. So, I guess I want to join Blueprint for its purpose, using the skills I have to help others.\n",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "In high school, I volunteered at my local YMCA as a child camp leader and I also participated in a lot of youth leadership conferences as a mentor. In addition, I also had the chance to be a part of our city’s multicultural youth council which focused on hosting events, workshops and conferences relating to the different cultures within our city, the culture of our own city and creating a space for youth to talk and discuss anything they wanted regarding their identity and culture. In university I worked as a organizer for Hack the North, but other than that I stopped actively participating within my community and doing pure volunteer work, which I really want to get back into.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Last year I was a designer/illustrator for Hack the North and I had the awesome opportunity to help rebuild and rebrand Hack the North with 4 other really cool designers. We developed everything including the typography, color usage, illustrations, the Hack the North homepage, online/mobile application experience, posters, apparel and swag items within a span of ​six months​. I’ve never worked on such a long term design project with such motivated people and I’m really proud of the fact that they gave me the trust to help build it.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I’m currently working on putting animations over the “Gonna Get Over You” music video by Sara Bareilles for fun. So far, I’ve produced a lot of neat gifs :) I’ll be happy to show them to you all!",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I can do both design and development as well as basic animation. I’m very comfortable designing, however I would like to improve my programming abilities and gain more confidence in that area!",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\Resume_2019.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F00fdf89e-607d-14ae-5b52-9410f117d313?alt=media&token=bd8ebb7f-5447-4764-91fa-f02a0228ea74",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F00fdf89e-607d-14ae-5b52-9410f117d313?alt=media&token=bd8ebb7f-5447-4764-91fa-f02a0228ea74",
        "roleQuestion1": "I think the standard answer most people will give including myself is that a powerful brand is a recognizable brand that is people centric and reflective of the values and culture of an organization. It’s something that people look forward to seeing and anticipating. However to add on to that, to me a brand becomes powerful when people begin associating it with a period of time in their life. When a brand becomes a nostalgic memory of the past or a remnant of childhood, that’s when I believe that the brand becomes more than just a visual identity and instead transcends its original purpose. ",
        "roleQuestion2": "https://graciexia.myportfolio.com/\n\nI illustrate a lot in my free time and I’m currently learning how to use After Effects to animate my illustrations to life, I keep online journal entries regarding my progress!\n\nhttps://gxiaaaa.tumblr.com/\n",
        "roleQuestion3": "Last summer I worked as a R&D developer at IFDS for my first co-op. I worked on developing a work object support tool which basically meant I created a lot of data visualizations and frontend items. I guess the entire process of developing the tool was a challenge. The data visualizations mocks required a lot of heavy custom javascript modifications in the charting library we used (d3.js) and there were times where I heavily struggled implementing the requirements. But in the end I was able to hand over a really cool deliverable and I found that the best way to overcome these technical challenges I faced was to look through a lot of Stack Overflow, read a lot of articles and books and never be afraid to ask stupid questions because that’s the best way to learn and grow.",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Content Director": "I think the standard answer most people will give including myself is that a powerful brand is a recognizable brand that is people centric and reflective of the values and culture of an organization. It’s something that people look forward to seeing and anticipating. However to add on to that, to me a brand becomes powerful when people begin associating it with a period of time in their life. When a brand becomes a nostalgic memory of the past or a remnant of childhood, that’s when I believe that the brand becomes more than just a visual identity and instead transcends its original purpose. ",
            "Product Designer": "https://graciexia.myportfolio.com/\n\nI illustrate a lot in my free time and I’m currently learning how to use After Effects to animate my illustrations to life, I keep online journal entries regarding my progress!\n\nhttps://gxiaaaa.tumblr.com/\n",
            "Project Developer": "Last summer I worked as a R&D developer at IFDS for my first co-op. I worked on developing a work object support tool which basically meant I created a lot of data visualizations and frontend items. I guess the entire process of developing the tool was a challenge. The data visualizations mocks required a lot of heavy custom javascript modifications in the charting library we used (d3.js) and there were times where I heavily struggled implementing the requirements. But in the end I was able to hand over a really cool deliverable and I found that the best way to overcome these technical challenges I faced was to look through a lot of Stack Overflow, read a lot of articles and books and never be afraid to ask stupid questions because that’s the best way to learn and grow."
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551294795940
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "1B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Other",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "kjiyee@edu.uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Krystal Jing Ing ",
        "lastName": "Yee",
        "positions": [
            "Product Manager",
            "VP External"
        ],
        "program": "Environment and Business",
        "question1": "I want to help people, also I will be on my summer break so I can dedicate my time to this fully. ",
        "question2": "College charity organizations (orphanage, terminally ill children) that gathered enough money for a fridge and provisions. High school charity (animal welfare) which lasted a whole year and raised 10k in donations. ",
        "question3": "I started a project with my charity club in college to raise money for the terminally ill children. We raised enough money to buy them a refrigerator and kettle that they needed. We had excess money in the treasury so we threw a small party with the children. As a group with a few volunteers we visited the children at the centre and bought some snacks. We also gave some party packs with colouring books and stickers inside for them. It was a touching moment hearing the children's parents tell us their stories. I was very proud that we were able to help them. ",
        "question4": "I have a baby sister who's 5 years old!",
        "question5": "",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I want to help people, also I will be on my summer break so I can dedicate my time to this fully. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "College charity organizations (orphanage, terminally ill children) that gathered enough money for a fridge and provisions. High school charity (animal welfare) which lasted a whole year and raised 10k in donations. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I started a project with my charity club in college to raise money for the terminally ill children. We raised enough money to buy them a refrigerator and kettle that they needed. We had excess money in the treasury so we threw a small party with the children. As a group with a few volunteers we visited the children at the centre and bought some snacks. We also gave some party packs with colouring books and stickers inside for them. It was a touching moment hearing the children's parents tell us their stories. I was very proud that we were able to help them. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I have a baby sister who's 5 years old!",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\Resume.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fb3dc52db-08d9-fff1-2556-6646d9c670fd?alt=media&token=fb1d7557-5fe2-43b1-862d-c69e69be21d5",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fb3dc52db-08d9-fff1-2556-6646d9c670fd?alt=media&token=fb1d7557-5fe2-43b1-862d-c69e69be21d5",
        "roleQuestion1": "",
        "roleQuestion2": "I don't particularly dislike any product, but I feel that cards are irrelevant. I would change it by creating a card that is able to combine all details and can attach to the back of any phone.  ",
        "roleQuestion3": "The non-profit would benefit blueprint and would be related to the goals that state that \"Blueprint strives to make technology accessible and useful for those who create communities and promote public welfare\". A non-profit would help with those who are limited in access to things as well as improve public service.\n",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Product Manager": "I don't particularly dislike any product, but I feel that cards are irrelevant. I would change it by creating a card that is able to combine all details and can attach to the back of any phone.  ",
            "VP External": "The non-profit would benefit blueprint and would be related to the goals that state that \"Blueprint strives to make technology accessible and useful for those who create communities and promote public welfare\". A non-profit would help with those who are limited in access to things as well as improve public service.\n"
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551407113703
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "1B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Co-op",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Co-op"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Clubs fair",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "hk4deol@edu.uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Harsukh",
        "lastName": "Deol",
        "positions": [
            "Product Designer"
        ],
        "program": "Mech Engineering",
        "question1": "Blueprint is such an amazing group that takes what they love and use it for social good. I want to join because I want to meet talented people who are ready to work hard to accomplish their dreams while leaving a positive impact where they go. I want to use my design skills to help people all over the world because I'm passionate about design and privileged to have the resources to follow it. I want to give back to the community and help people be the best they can be. I care about environmental sustainability, feminism and equality for all living things in general, so I'm excited to discover how I can use my design skills to improve these issues.",
        "question2": "Currently, I'm a member of FemPhys, a feminist physics club at UW that runs events for various topics related to females, visible minorities and the LGBTQ+ community in science. Recently, I made artwork for a non-profit magazine that spreads awareness about the issues females, people of color and LGBTQ+ community face. I was an executive of the DECA chapter in my high school. DECA is a non-profit student organization that runs competitions about a variety of business topics. I was the marketing lead, so I present the club at open houses, managed social media and created appealing posters. I also planned and taught lessons to members of the chapter. Moreover, I volunteered at SUYVA which is a volunteering organization that plans impactful events for high school students. I planned a literacy event with a scavenger hunt, guest speaker and board games. I spent a summer volunteering at my library as a program assistant. Here I lead STEM events for school aged children and helped the library staff with administration tasks.",
        "question3": "I coded a Harry Potter game similar to Pottermore. Here I created a interactive sorting hat quiz with a visually appealing interface. Each question and button had its own background image and at the end a picture of your house popped up with your house. I also created a Potions minigame where there were image buttons for the recipe, each ingredient, stirring and waving the wand. I created an animation for the stirring and the wand waving to add more visual appeal. I programmed a Dueling game where the user had to click a sequence of buttons in a limited amount of time or they would get jinxed. I had the screen flash and become white if the user was hit with a spell. Lastly, I included a Quidditch game where you could move your player with the arrow keys to catch the snitch while avoiding the blundgers. ",
        "question4": " I love dancing and cooking food! I used to make jewelry for fun and architecture models in high school. I also designed my school yearbook and posters for 7 clubs. ",
        "question5": "I want to make more designer and programmer friends! I'm in mechanical engineering so alot of my friends are more into machinery than UI/UX design. I want to have a group of people who I can share the latest web design trends with and ask for advice on how to improve my designs and advance as a designer. I also want to be around like-minded people who live with a positive attitude towards university and get excited when presented a good challenge. ",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "Blueprint is such an amazing group that takes what they love and use it for social good. I want to join because I want to meet talented people who are ready to work hard to accomplish their dreams while leaving a positive impact where they go. I want to use my design skills to help people all over the world because I'm passionate about design and privileged to have the resources to follow it. I want to give back to the community and help people be the best they can be. I care about environmental sustainability, feminism and equality for all living things in general, so I'm excited to discover how I can use my design skills to improve these issues.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Currently, I'm a member of FemPhys, a feminist physics club at UW that runs events for various topics related to females, visible minorities and the LGBTQ+ community in science. Recently, I made artwork for a non-profit magazine that spreads awareness about the issues females, people of color and LGBTQ+ community face. I was an executive of the DECA chapter in my high school. DECA is a non-profit student organization that runs competitions about a variety of business topics. I was the marketing lead, so I present the club at open houses, managed social media and created appealing posters. I also planned and taught lessons to members of the chapter. Moreover, I volunteered at SUYVA which is a volunteering organization that plans impactful events for high school students. I planned a literacy event with a scavenger hunt, guest speaker and board games. I spent a summer volunteering at my library as a program assistant. Here I lead STEM events for school aged children and helped the library staff with administration tasks.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I coded a Harry Potter game similar to Pottermore. Here I created a interactive sorting hat quiz with a visually appealing interface. Each question and button had its own background image and at the end a picture of your house popped up with your house. I also created a Potions minigame where there were image buttons for the recipe, each ingredient, stirring and waving the wand. I created an animation for the stirring and the wand waving to add more visual appeal. I programmed a Dueling game where the user had to click a sequence of buttons in a limited amount of time or they would get jinxed. I had the screen flash and become white if the user was hit with a spell. Lastly, I included a Quidditch game where you could move your player with the arrow keys to catch the snitch while avoiding the blundgers. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": " I love dancing and cooking food! I used to make jewelry for fun and architecture models in high school. I also designed my school yearbook and posters for 7 clubs. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I want to make more designer and programmer friends! I'm in mechanical engineering so alot of my friends are more into machinery than UI/UX design. I want to have a group of people who I can share the latest web design trends with and ask for advice on how to improve my designs and advance as a designer. I also want to be around like-minded people who live with a positive attitude towards university and get excited when presented a good challenge. ",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\resume.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fd4ad1fc9-4bdd-ac0f-806d-a7a9995e9fe6?alt=media&token=721a87ed-6976-4979-9a0a-a1284b7835d5",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fd4ad1fc9-4bdd-ac0f-806d-a7a9995e9fe6?alt=media&token=721a87ed-6976-4979-9a0a-a1284b7835d5",
        "roleQuestion1": "I make graphic art and post it on insta : @goldencentaur\nhttps://www.instagram.com/goldencentaur/?hl=en\n\nMy first version of my website (working on adding animations right now):\nhttps://harsukhdeol.github.io/me/\n",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Product Designer": "I make graphic art and post it on insta : @goldencentaur\nhttps://www.instagram.com/goldencentaur/?hl=en\n\nMy first version of my website (working on adding animations right now):\nhttps://harsukhdeol.github.io/me/\n"
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551553582266
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "1B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Co-op",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Co-op"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Other",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "charlesdobson92@gmail.com",
        "firstName": "Charles",
        "lastName": "Dobson",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer"
        ],
        "program": "Software Engineering Technology (Conestoga College)",
        "question1": "I would love to collaborate with people interested in volunteering in tech. I'm new to development and think that Blueprint would be a great way to progress my skills while contributing to something meaningful.",
        "question2": "I'm currently a member of the Leadership Ambassadors at Conestoga College. We collaborate as a team to brainstorm, facilitate and execute volunteer initiatives for the college and the local community. Last semester, I helped organize, promote and execute a food drive for the Conestoga Food Bank. Most recently, I helped by promoting and collecting items for a \"Hygiene for the Homeless\" campaign to provide homeless shelters in the Waterloo region with necessities. We successfully supplied 1500+ items for those in need.",
        "question3": "Although I am relatively new to programming, I'm quite passionate about learning through side projects. I've developed a few security/cryptography related programs, including a cypher program to encode messages using the Vigenere and RSA algorithms and a simple keylogger implemented in Python.\n\nI'm currently building a portfolio website to showcase my current and future projects. ",
        "question4": "Snails can sleep for up to 3 years at a time",
        "question5": "Although I'm not a University of Waterloo student, I am passionate about the tech community and looking to collaborate on exciting new projects with people in the Waterloo region. \n\nIn the Software Engineering Technology program at Conestoga College, I have developed an understanding of C and C++. On my own, I have developed an understanding of HTML, CSS, Python and some Javascript.",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I would love to collaborate with people interested in volunteering in tech. I'm new to development and think that Blueprint would be a great way to progress my skills while contributing to something meaningful.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I'm currently a member of the Leadership Ambassadors at Conestoga College. We collaborate as a team to brainstorm, facilitate and execute volunteer initiatives for the college and the local community. Last semester, I helped organize, promote and execute a food drive for the Conestoga Food Bank. Most recently, I helped by promoting and collecting items for a \"Hygiene for the Homeless\" campaign to provide homeless shelters in the Waterloo region with necessities. We successfully supplied 1500+ items for those in need.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Although I am relatively new to programming, I'm quite passionate about learning through side projects. I've developed a few security/cryptography related programs, including a cypher program to encode messages using the Vigenere and RSA algorithms and a simple keylogger implemented in Python.\n\nI'm currently building a portfolio website to showcase my current and future projects. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Snails can sleep for up to 3 years at a time",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Although I'm not a University of Waterloo student, I am passionate about the tech community and looking to collaborate on exciting new projects with people in the Waterloo region. \n\nIn the Software Engineering Technology program at Conestoga College, I have developed an understanding of C and C++. On my own, I have developed an understanding of HTML, CSS, Python and some Javascript.",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\Resume - Charles Dobson.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F82230746-d998-eb76-eac1-93be84a06d95?alt=media&token=34a8135c-ac9d-43ea-afea-3c7a9931ff24",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F82230746-d998-eb76-eac1-93be84a06d95?alt=media&token=34a8135c-ac9d-43ea-afea-3c7a9931ff24",
        "roleQuestion1": "Transitioning from a technical, hands-on trade in the military to a career in software development has been an interesting journey. Initially, I decided to complete a Front End Web Development certificate on freeCodeCamp. It was a steep learning curve for me and I often came up with excuses as to why I couldn't finish. Through perseverance, I was able to complete the certificate and learned a lot in the process. Since then, I have been passionate about learning as much as possible about the programming world and don't plan on stopping anytime soon. My diagnostic knowledge and practised problem-solving techniques have proved to be invaluable in software development.",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "Transitioning from a technical, hands-on trade in the military to a career in software development has been an interesting journey. Initially, I decided to complete a Front End Web Development certificate on freeCodeCamp. It was a steep learning curve for me and I often came up with excuses as to why I couldn't finish. Through perseverance, I was able to complete the certificate and learned a lot in the process. Since then, I have been passionate about learning as much as possible about the programming world and don't plan on stopping anytime soon. My diagnostic knowledge and practised problem-solving techniques have proved to be invaluable in software development."
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551644689125
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "4A",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Facebook",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "r255zhan@edu.uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Rui",
        "lastName": "Zhang",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer"
        ],
        "program": "Management Engineering",
        "question1": "I would like to start giving back to the community with the software development knowledge I have learned through academics and co-op.",
        "question2": "I will help with the technical development process onprojects",
        "question3": "I have built a search engine using Java from scratch ",
        "question4": "I can't sleep if my code doesn't work :( ",
        "question5": "",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I would like to start giving back to the community with the software development knowledge I have learned through academics and co-op.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I will help with the technical development process onprojects",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I have built a search engine using Java from scratch ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I can't sleep if my code doesn't work :( ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\David Zhang - Resume (1).pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F9293ee61-4aff-7a71-bc91-b402aa994bb8?alt=media&token=710c32cc-b60b-484c-afb8-8eecbce0c10a",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F9293ee61-4aff-7a71-bc91-b402aa994bb8?alt=media&token=710c32cc-b60b-484c-afb8-8eecbce0c10a",
        "roleQuestion1": "I had to implement flash notification during work. Given that the website used React SSR, the notifications had to be dispatched whenever a user updates the profile settings. Therefore, I had to conceptually understand Redux's middleware: Saga and generator functions. Afterwards I had to implement it in a scale-able way. ",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "I had to implement flash notification during work. Given that the website used React SSR, the notifications had to be dispatched whenever a user updates the profile settings. Therefore, I had to conceptually understand Redux's middleware: Saga and generator functions. Afterwards I had to implement it in a scale-able way. "
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551645965597
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "2A",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Word of mouth",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "prachi.gupta@edu.uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Prachi",
        "lastName": "Gupta",
        "positions": [
            "Product Designer"
        ],
        "program": "Economics, CS Minor (Coop)",
        "question1": "UW Blueprint to me has always come off as an environment where intellectually like minded people come together to use their skills, learn and build projects for teams and visions that need it. I’ve always been the sort of person who loves working in a team of people that will get things done but also go out for dinners and karaoke, and from all my friends’ stories that have worked with blueprint, it seems like the perfect fit for me. I wish to be a part of the team because I tend to only pursue projects that I know mean something to me, and I have emotional reasons to continue pursuing and working hard towards, things that make me want to stay up even when I’m tired to make sure the task gets done. Having followed blueprint for a long time, reading stories by past members, I see that with the team I’d be able to connect with and learn about multiple local communities, and take a project from an idea to endgame within a short period of time, and at the same time enrich my school life.",
        "question2": "As the current Digital X Head for Fashion for Change, an on campus organization that hosts a fashion show to fundraise for WE Charity, I’m constantly exposed to different ways of using digital trends to raise money for the charity (such as online auctions, websites etc). Doing so makes the tasks worthwhile and helps me encourage the team even further to work hard. This made me realise that I enjoy volunteer work loads but in ways where I can use my learnings and build on my skills at the same time, sort of a mutually beneficial relationship. With blueprint I’ll be able to do the exact same!",
        "question3": "At my position with Corby, I was given the opportunity to take full control of my tasks, but the one that stood out was the last one that I took on, which not only was very fulfilling professionally, but it allowed me to learn exactly how I should go about choosing the tasks/teams/events I pursue. As a 2 person core tech team with my boss, we naturally had a lot of tasks to divide between us, and when he was on vacation in August, I had to take on the role. At the same time I was working on a heavy data migration task with the Parisian team, and because of how welcoming, supportive, exciting and intellectually challenging the environment was at Corby, I found myself waking up at 4 am to work with the Parisian team, because I wanted to get the tasks done as fast as possible. I realized that I had teams dependent on me, and even though I was overloaded with work, I was never made to feel like I couldn’t ask for help or questions. I’m proud of this one period of my professional life because this was the first time I was able to decide what at the minimum I want from the teams I work with and what sort of roles I would be interested in!",
        "question4": "I started learning ice skating this January and one of my long term goals for this year is to be a *beginner/good enough* figure skater (who can at the very least jump spin on ice)!\nI also have 3 tiny tattoos and want to get more :D",
        "question5": "The reason I’m pursuing the product designer role with Blueprint is because I’ve found that it’s the path for me going forward. From learning calligraphy and creating random graphic art through high school, and now working on various teams on website mockups, illustrations, animation updates, to even working on my own personal website, or designing my resume, I enjoy being able to learn about what exactly the task requires (goals, vision, research oriented efforts) and then working on building a product that the team I’m working with looks at and sees that it perfectly reflects what our vision started out to be. Being able to work with non profit organizations would give me to opportunity to learn from and work with such teams and take projects through these progressions!",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "UW Blueprint to me has always come off as an environment where intellectually like minded people come together to use their skills, learn and build projects for teams and visions that need it. I’ve always been the sort of person who loves working in a team of people that will get things done but also go out for dinners and karaoke, and from all my friends’ stories that have worked with blueprint, it seems like the perfect fit for me. I wish to be a part of the team because I tend to only pursue projects that I know mean something to me, and I have emotional reasons to continue pursuing and working hard towards, things that make me want to stay up even when I’m tired to make sure the task gets done. Having followed blueprint for a long time, reading stories by past members, I see that with the team I’d be able to connect with and learn about multiple local communities, and take a project from an idea to endgame within a short period of time, and at the same time enrich my school life.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "As the current Digital X Head for Fashion for Change, an on campus organization that hosts a fashion show to fundraise for WE Charity, I’m constantly exposed to different ways of using digital trends to raise money for the charity (such as online auctions, websites etc). Doing so makes the tasks worthwhile and helps me encourage the team even further to work hard. This made me realise that I enjoy volunteer work loads but in ways where I can use my learnings and build on my skills at the same time, sort of a mutually beneficial relationship. With blueprint I’ll be able to do the exact same!",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "At my position with Corby, I was given the opportunity to take full control of my tasks, but the one that stood out was the last one that I took on, which not only was very fulfilling professionally, but it allowed me to learn exactly how I should go about choosing the tasks/teams/events I pursue. As a 2 person core tech team with my boss, we naturally had a lot of tasks to divide between us, and when he was on vacation in August, I had to take on the role. At the same time I was working on a heavy data migration task with the Parisian team, and because of how welcoming, supportive, exciting and intellectually challenging the environment was at Corby, I found myself waking up at 4 am to work with the Parisian team, because I wanted to get the tasks done as fast as possible. I realized that I had teams dependent on me, and even though I was overloaded with work, I was never made to feel like I couldn’t ask for help or questions. I’m proud of this one period of my professional life because this was the first time I was able to decide what at the minimum I want from the teams I work with and what sort of roles I would be interested in!",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I started learning ice skating this January and one of my long term goals for this year is to be a *beginner/good enough* figure skater (who can at the very least jump spin on ice)!\nI also have 3 tiny tattoos and want to get more :D",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "The reason I’m pursuing the product designer role with Blueprint is because I’ve found that it’s the path for me going forward. From learning calligraphy and creating random graphic art through high school, and now working on various teams on website mockups, illustrations, animation updates, to even working on my own personal website, or designing my resume, I enjoy being able to learn about what exactly the task requires (goals, vision, research oriented efforts) and then working on building a product that the team I’m working with looks at and sees that it perfectly reflects what our vision started out to be. Being able to work with non profit organizations would give me to opportunity to learn from and work with such teams and take projects through these progressions!",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F7d544dea-f330-b440-6329-b7cec4e2735f?alt=media&token=de3f8d0a-8545-46c9-954f-f1978e72c665",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F7d544dea-f330-b440-6329-b7cec4e2735f?alt=media&token=de3f8d0a-8545-46c9-954f-f1978e72c665",
        "roleQuestion1": "https://prachig.com",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Product Designer": "https://prachig.com"
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551648206767
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "1B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Other",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "borismiler1@gmail.com",
        "firstName": "Boris ",
        "lastName": "Miler",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer",
            "Product Designer",
            "Project Lead",
            "Product Manager"
        ],
        "program": "Honours Mathematics",
        "question1": "I wish to meet new people and be able to express creative ideas and have the ability to work and collaborate with such an interesting team.  I believe Blueprint has the ability, which is clearly shown by your other projects, to achieve great things.  An experience with Blueprint would be an experience to remember with many learning opportunities.  ",
        "question2": "Elementary school book fair, high school volunteering, volunteered for a painting company, volunteered for a property management company.",
        "question3": "Me and a group of friends in high school built a simple app for the high school's students to use.",
        "question4": "I ate the world's spiciest pepper: The Carolina Reaper.",
        "question5": "",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I wish to meet new people and be able to express creative ideas and have the ability to work and collaborate with such an interesting team.  I believe Blueprint has the ability, which is clearly shown by your other projects, to achieve great things.  An experience with Blueprint would be an experience to remember with many learning opportunities.  ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Elementary school book fair, high school volunteering, volunteered for a painting company, volunteered for a property management company.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Me and a group of friends in high school built a simple app for the high school's students to use.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I ate the world's spiciest pepper: The Carolina Reaper.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\Boris' actual resume.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fb202a606-83ad-d6cc-ba3f-f6a3b8417040?alt=media&token=3fc637fd-7448-4ba7-9ceb-ce947d3345f4",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fb202a606-83ad-d6cc-ba3f-f6a3b8417040?alt=media&token=3fc637fd-7448-4ba7-9ceb-ce947d3345f4",
        "roleQuestion1": "A technical challenge I faces was collaborating with a completely different team, which created the art and designed the work for our product; an iOS application.  The art team's creations had to be implemented using Swift in a way which was pleasing to both the artists, developers and the audience.  Learning Swift and learning how to implement the code to achieve what the artist's designed was met with many management discussions.  Eventually, after our discussions, the coding team was able to use online resources which allowed the team to properly integrate the design and art into the app.",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "I dislike the headphones I am currently wearing.  The padding around the ears is not sufficient and they do not enclose the entire ear.  Also, the padding on top of my head is lacking and is beginning to hurt.  I would definitely use a better material, not cheap plastic; use more padding at the top and make the ear cups much larger.",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Product Designer": "",
            "Product Manager": "I dislike the headphones I am currently wearing.  The padding around the ears is not sufficient and they do not enclose the entire ear.  Also, the padding on top of my head is lacking and is beginning to hurt.  I would definitely use a better material, not cheap plastic; use more padding at the top and make the ear cups much larger.",
            "Project Developer": "A technical challenge I faces was collaborating with a completely different team, which created the art and designed the work for our product; an iOS application.  The art team's creations had to be implemented using Swift in a way which was pleasing to both the artists, developers and the audience.  Learning Swift and learning how to implement the code to achieve what the artist's designed was met with many management discussions.  Eventually, after our discussions, the coding team was able to use online resources which allowed the team to properly integrate the design and art into the app."
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551667003822
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "2B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Co-op",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Co-op"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Word of mouth",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "alexieyizhe@gmail.com",
        "firstName": "Alex",
        "lastName": "Xie",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer",
            "Project Lead"
        ],
        "program": "Computer Science",
        "question1": "I believe that much like any product or service that a company provides, I can always improve. I also understand that I still have a tremendous amount to learn; that has always been what I hope to achieve in any leadership opportunity and I am excited about the growth that working with Blueprint can entail, with all the talented peers I can learn from.",
        "question2": "I am the Dev Lead for Equithon, a social innovation hackathon non-profit that's aiming to help improve and provide solutions for a huge range of social equity issues, like economic disparity and physical disabilities. \n\nOn my co-op term, I visited the Ronald McDonald house in Toronto to help prepare and serve hot meals for the residents, and it was an amazing experience that really helped me see how providing a place of comfort for anxious parents and their children away from home can improve their spirits immensely.\n\nI also volunteered extensively in the past with my local library, grassroots soccer, and as an executive for a Christmas party that we hold annually for underprivileged inner city children.",
        "question3": "A project that I'm the most proud of is the Equithon personal dashboard site, soon to be live at my.equithon.org. Our goal for this year's Equithon is to have a centralized location for information and actions that attendees can take, whether it's filling out an application or judging projects at the actual event.\n\nI learned a great deal about UI/UX design tools, and an even greater amount about building dynamic interactive websites with React, Redux, and dealing with a service like Firebase. ",
        "question4": "i liek de bad puns",
        "question5": "",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I believe that much like any product or service that a company provides, I can always improve. I also understand that I still have a tremendous amount to learn; that has always been what I hope to achieve in any leadership opportunity and I am excited about the growth that working with Blueprint can entail, with all the talented peers I can learn from.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I am the Dev Lead for Equithon, a social innovation hackathon non-profit that's aiming to help improve and provide solutions for a huge range of social equity issues, like economic disparity and physical disabilities. \n\nOn my co-op term, I visited the Ronald McDonald house in Toronto to help prepare and serve hot meals for the residents, and it was an amazing experience that really helped me see how providing a place of comfort for anxious parents and their children away from home can improve their spirits immensely.\n\nI also volunteered extensively in the past with my local library, grassroots soccer, and as an executive for a Christmas party that we hold annually for underprivileged inner city children.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "A project that I'm the most proud of is the Equithon personal dashboard site, soon to be live at my.equithon.org. Our goal for this year's Equithon is to have a centralized location for information and actions that attendees can take, whether it's filling out an application or judging projects at the actual event.\n\nI learned a great deal about UI/UX design tools, and an even greater amount about building dynamic interactive websites with React, Redux, and dealing with a service like Firebase. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "i liek de bad puns",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\Resume (Current).pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F09370fab-cbb0-54d4-51ba-966286a59830?alt=media&token=feb9fb63-cbb1-4a3b-ba84-c156bfa6c9d6",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F09370fab-cbb0-54d4-51ba-966286a59830?alt=media&token=feb9fb63-cbb1-4a3b-ba84-c156bfa6c9d6",
        "roleQuestion1": "A huge technical challenge was learning the ins and outs of Firebase. I was unfamiliar with interfacing with a serverless backend like Firebase, and was accustomed to working with a backend API that I can query and customize to fit my needs.\n\nWhile Firebase is incredibly powerful and offers so many useful services that are hard to set up on their own, there's a bit of learning curve that accompanies that many features. I had to learn how to incorporate Firebase's Auth and noSQL Firestore DB with the functional components using React hooks, which was very satisfying to solve. I did so by wrapping my calls to Firebase in a class and using a custom hook to re-render the component when the class instance changed, allowing me to preserve features and makes it easier to work with.",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "A huge technical challenge was learning the ins and outs of Firebase. I was unfamiliar with interfacing with a serverless backend like Firebase, and was accustomed to working with a backend API that I can query and customize to fit my needs.\n\nWhile Firebase is incredibly powerful and offers so many useful services that are hard to set up on their own, there's a bit of learning curve that accompanies that many features. I had to learn how to incorporate Firebase's Auth and noSQL Firestore DB with the functional components using React hooks, which was very satisfying to solve. I did so by wrapping my calls to Firebase in a class and using a custom hook to re-render the component when the class instance changed, allowing me to preserve features and makes it easier to work with."
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551673225953
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "2B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Other",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "gmudbhat@uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Gaurav",
        "lastName": "Mudbhatkal",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer"
        ],
        "program": "Management Engineering",
        "question1": "I want to be a part of the team because I believe that the objective of Blueprint is very unique compared to other non-profits and clubs. With Blueprint, I will be able to make a positive impact on a lot of people, and at the same time, improve my skills and possibly get to learn some new ones from my teammates. After taking a look at the current and past projects that the teams have been working on, I can't wait to get started!",
        "question2": "Since coming to the University of Waterloo, unfortunately, I have not been part of any non-profits. In my high school days, I have participated in collecting donations for victims of natural disaster and volunteered for most of the events that were held by my high school(talent shows, sports days, vaccination drives, exhibitions, etc.)",
        "question3": "A project that I am most proud of was a Decision Support Tool that I had created in my first term at UW. It wasn't the most 'difficult' project(content wise) that I have been a part of, but it was the conditions that it was set in that made it one of the trickiest. My team consisted of people that I had met for the first time, and the topic that was given to us was very vague- we had no idea of how to start, and even after coming up with a plan, there were many days where we weren't sure if it was the right one. But, by the end of the term, we were able to come up with we had imagined at the start and were immensely proud of it.",
        "question4": "I have lived in one of the hottest countries in the world(Qatar, where temperatures go up to 50C), as well as one of the coldest countries in the world(Canada, where I got to experience -30C weather this winter!)",
        "question5": "I am currently on a co-op term and haven't updated my resume with this work experience yet. Just want to give you a few details:\nI am working as a Data Analytics Co-op student at BBM Canada. I have learned to code in Scala and have gained experience in working with a complex data pipeline. In this term, I have also learned to properly use Git as a version control tool.",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I want to be a part of the team because I believe that the objective of Blueprint is very unique compared to other non-profits and clubs. With Blueprint, I will be able to make a positive impact on a lot of people, and at the same time, improve my skills and possibly get to learn some new ones from my teammates. After taking a look at the current and past projects that the teams have been working on, I can't wait to get started!",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Since coming to the University of Waterloo, unfortunately, I have not been part of any non-profits. In my high school days, I have participated in collecting donations for victims of natural disaster and volunteered for most of the events that were held by my high school(talent shows, sports days, vaccination drives, exhibitions, etc.)",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "A project that I am most proud of was a Decision Support Tool that I had created in my first term at UW. It wasn't the most 'difficult' project(content wise) that I have been a part of, but it was the conditions that it was set in that made it one of the trickiest. My team consisted of people that I had met for the first time, and the topic that was given to us was very vague- we had no idea of how to start, and even after coming up with a plan, there were many days where we weren't sure if it was the right one. But, by the end of the term, we were able to come up with we had imagined at the start and were immensely proud of it.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I have lived in one of the hottest countries in the world(Qatar, where temperatures go up to 50C), as well as one of the coldest countries in the world(Canada, where I got to experience -30C weather this winter!)",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I am currently on a co-op term and haven't updated my resume with this work experience yet. Just want to give you a few details:\nI am working as a Data Analytics Co-op student at BBM Canada. I have learned to code in Scala and have gained experience in working with a complex data pipeline. In this term, I have also learned to properly use Git as a version control tool.",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\Gaurav_tech.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F6a74d8e2-9331-9302-5c84-ac2d9373e7a9?alt=media&token=03dfdf30-1372-463b-b619-304c46c73f30",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F6a74d8e2-9331-9302-5c84-ac2d9373e7a9?alt=media&token=03dfdf30-1372-463b-b619-304c46c73f30",
        "roleQuestion1": "On my current co-op term, one of my tasks was to modify a casting function that was causing a lot of table schemas to change. Making the change was easy, but since this was a utility function, it was used in a lot of different transforms and tests. So, naturally, these tests started to fail. At first, I was overwhelmed by the number of tests that were failing and was contemplating whether making the change was worth it. But upon closer observation of these tests, I saw that only small bits of code were causing these failures and they were easy to fix. This taught me to keep looking for solutions, no matter how big/tough the task may be.",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "On my current co-op term, one of my tasks was to modify a casting function that was causing a lot of table schemas to change. Making the change was easy, but since this was a utility function, it was used in a lot of different transforms and tests. So, naturally, these tests started to fail. At first, I was overwhelmed by the number of tests that were failing and was contemplating whether making the change was worth it. But upon closer observation of these tests, I saw that only small bits of code were causing these failures and they were easy to fix. This taught me to keep looking for solutions, no matter how big/tough the task may be."
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551751683554
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "2B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Facebook",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "f49wu@uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Fangyu",
        "lastName": "Wu",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer",
            "Project Lead",
            "Product Manager"
        ],
        "program": "Computer Science",
        "question1": "I have a great great passion for building social good that could have significant impact! Building a successful product is my biggest passion and it will give a lot of sense of achievement. And I really enjoy the time when I could work with group of young people focusing on a meaningful project. (such as a hackathon which I have been to lot)  I also hope I could gain more experience and learn some new skills from the club's members. ",
        "question2": "Last summer, I worked as a volunteer in Canada Day Celebration Event at the university. I worked with other members in the \"spirit squad\" team and helped with the preparation of the entire event in 3 days including clean up waste and taking commemorative photos with kids. That was really enjoyable and I had a lot of fun from that event.",
        "question3": "I built a real-time white-board sharing and video calling iOS app last December during a hackathon. I actually really like that project since it is really helpful when I want to talk about some math/cs questions with my friend.  ",
        "question4": "I really like the colour of the Blueprint logo, it's really adorable. ",
        "question5": "",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I have a great great passion for building social good that could have significant impact! Building a successful product is my biggest passion and it will give a lot of sense of achievement. And I really enjoy the time when I could work with group of young people focusing on a meaningful project. (such as a hackathon which I have been to lot)  I also hope I could gain more experience and learn some new skills from the club's members. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Last summer, I worked as a volunteer in Canada Day Celebration Event at the university. I worked with other members in the \"spirit squad\" team and helped with the preparation of the entire event in 3 days including clean up waste and taking commemorative photos with kids. That was really enjoyable and I had a lot of fun from that event.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I built a real-time white-board sharing and video calling iOS app last December during a hackathon. I actually really like that project since it is really helpful when I want to talk about some math/cs questions with my friend.  ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I really like the colour of the Blueprint logo, it's really adorable. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\FangyuWu.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F5840585a-5391-145f-7290-91dd3c8fc472?alt=media&token=c8c22c73-cfa6-43f1-8dcf-6a5d8ddf503f",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F5840585a-5391-145f-7290-91dd3c8fc472?alt=media&token=c8c22c73-cfa6-43f1-8dcf-6a5d8ddf503f",
        "roleQuestion1": "I got tons of technical challenges during my first internship. One of those challenges I got is that I need to set up a telemetry collector for request telemetry collection into 10+ different large-scale web services (including Wcf services, webAPI, IIS serivces...). And I had no experiences about how those services works. Instead of just going directly to google and search \"how to set up telemetry collector into xxx services\",  I spend some time trying to understand the mechanism of those different type of services. And this helped a lot when I start troubleshooting the problem into those different services. ",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Product Manager": "",
            "Project Developer": "I got tons of technical challenges during my first internship. One of those challenges I got is that I need to set up a telemetry collector for request telemetry collection into 10+ different large-scale web services (including Wcf services, webAPI, IIS serivces...). And I had no experiences about how those services works. Instead of just going directly to google and search \"how to set up telemetry collector into xxx services\",  I spend some time trying to understand the mechanism of those different type of services. And this helped a lot when I start troubleshooting the problem into those different services. "
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551755668898
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "3A",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Word of mouth",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "edan@edu.uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Eric",
        "lastName": "Dan",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer",
            "Project Lead"
        ],
        "program": "Computer Science",
        "question1": "I'd like to use the skills I've learned in school and co-op to give back to the community as well as expand my professional network within UW",
        "question2": "I participate in Random Hacks of Kindness, a hackathon that gathers volunteer and non-profit organizations and matches them with developers to produce MVPs for tools they need but don't have the knowledge to build",
        "question3": "I created a web app that allows users edit and display sequences of timed annotations on embedded YouTube videos. Part of what made this project special to me is that it solved a problem I had been personally facing for a while, which was the difficulty involved in getting people to review and analyze recordings of my tournament play in order to improve my skills in Super Smash Bros.",
        "question4": "I'm ranked in the top 10 Super Smash Bros Melee players in Waterloo ;)",
        "question5": "",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I'd like to use the skills I've learned in school and co-op to give back to the community as well as expand my professional network within UW",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I participate in Random Hacks of Kindness, a hackathon that gathers volunteer and non-profit organizations and matches them with developers to produce MVPs for tools they need but don't have the knowledge to build",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I created a web app that allows users edit and display sequences of timed annotations on embedded YouTube videos. Part of what made this project special to me is that it solved a problem I had been personally facing for a while, which was the difficulty involved in getting people to review and analyze recordings of my tournament play in order to improve my skills in Super Smash Bros.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I'm ranked in the top 10 Super Smash Bros Melee players in Waterloo ;)",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\EricDan_Resume_3A_1.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F5511a553-068f-1456-6795-5c5292414dcf?alt=media&token=8a2c2e57-a7a4-4fb5-acbf-e41c5cf8797b",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F5511a553-068f-1456-6795-5c5292414dcf?alt=media&token=8a2c2e57-a7a4-4fb5-acbf-e41c5cf8797b",
        "roleQuestion1": "Recently at my internship, an important bug was discovered that had been negatively affecting the company's financials for a few weeks. I consolidated data and knowledge from a multitude of sources including server logs, database entity change logs, and knowledge of systems from multiple senior engineers in order to determine the root cause of the problem, and corrected the mistakes made. ",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "Recently at my internship, an important bug was discovered that had been negatively affecting the company's financials for a few weeks. I consolidated data and knowledge from a multitude of sources including server logs, database entity change logs, and knowledge of systems from multiple senior engineers in order to determine the root cause of the problem, and corrected the mistakes made. "
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551756469629
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "2A",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Co-op",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Co-op"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Word of mouth",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "jayant.shrivastava@uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Jayant",
        "lastName": "Shrivastava",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer"
        ],
        "program": "Computer Engineering ",
        "question1": "I believe that I’m a strong developer, and I ultimately want to use my passion for tech to make a positive impact in the world. I have always had a passion for volunteerism and promoting social good, accumulating 1000 volunteer hours in high school. After reading about Blueprint projects, I was fascinated by the social problems that local organizations are solving and really wanted to get involved. When I looked over Blueprint’s Github and spoke to friends on the team, I got a sense of how Blueprint increases the impact of each organization by building tools for metrics, data analysis and more. I think I have a strong skill set including backend, infrastructure, and even data skills that would make me an outstanding member of Blueprint, and I would love to be a part of team!",
        "question2": "I was an active member of the Markham Youth Council for 4 years, and I was the council chair in grade 11. I lead a group of 50 high school students in hosting events in our community to promote youth activism. We held competitions, coffee houses, and workshops to encourage students to connect with each other and unite to fundraise for NPOs such as the Cancer Recovery Foundation of Canada. I also actively volunteered for the Markham Stouffville Hospital Foundation which was a non-profit branch of the hospital dedicated to fundraising for improving patient experiences. To raise funds for new equipment and patient facilities at the hospital, I helped organize events such gift wrapping stations at local malls during the holidays and skills workshops for students.",
        "question3": "Doctor DMs is a serverless, text messaging medical diagnosis and treatment service I programed using Node. My goal for this project was to make health resources accessible to those who aren’t fortunate enough to have internet access, emergency medical services, and health education. In fact, a 2014 survey found that 80% of households in rural Bangladesh have cellphones despite lacking basic necessities such as clean water and health services. Doctor DMs provides a text messaging interface that can be queried with symptoms that it responds to with diagnoses and percentage likelihood ratings. It also provides treatment information and descriptions of diseases. You can try out the service by texting 1+ 204 818 5344 and check out the code at github.com/jayshrivastava/doctor-dms",
        "question4": "I am an avid smash player and I won the ECE Smash Ultimate tournament in February! \n",
        "question5": "",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I believe that I’m a strong developer, and I ultimately want to use my passion for tech to make a positive impact in the world. I have always had a passion for volunteerism and promoting social good, accumulating 1000 volunteer hours in high school. After reading about Blueprint projects, I was fascinated by the social problems that local organizations are solving and really wanted to get involved. When I looked over Blueprint’s Github and spoke to friends on the team, I got a sense of how Blueprint increases the impact of each organization by building tools for metrics, data analysis and more. I think I have a strong skill set including backend, infrastructure, and even data skills that would make me an outstanding member of Blueprint, and I would love to be a part of team!",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I was an active member of the Markham Youth Council for 4 years, and I was the council chair in grade 11. I lead a group of 50 high school students in hosting events in our community to promote youth activism. We held competitions, coffee houses, and workshops to encourage students to connect with each other and unite to fundraise for NPOs such as the Cancer Recovery Foundation of Canada. I also actively volunteered for the Markham Stouffville Hospital Foundation which was a non-profit branch of the hospital dedicated to fundraising for improving patient experiences. To raise funds for new equipment and patient facilities at the hospital, I helped organize events such gift wrapping stations at local malls during the holidays and skills workshops for students.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Doctor DMs is a serverless, text messaging medical diagnosis and treatment service I programed using Node. My goal for this project was to make health resources accessible to those who aren’t fortunate enough to have internet access, emergency medical services, and health education. In fact, a 2014 survey found that 80% of households in rural Bangladesh have cellphones despite lacking basic necessities such as clean water and health services. Doctor DMs provides a text messaging interface that can be queried with symptoms that it responds to with diagnoses and percentage likelihood ratings. It also provides treatment information and descriptions of diseases. You can try out the service by texting 1+ 204 818 5344 and check out the code at github.com/jayshrivastava/doctor-dms",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I am an avid smash player and I won the ECE Smash Ultimate tournament in February! \n",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\Jayant-Shrivastava-Resume-SE-2019-v2.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F36aabc82-1295-9b2d-c863-9f97563c1e4c?alt=media&token=b88c20ee-ae78-4529-9480-f3b3b0ad1d45",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F36aabc82-1295-9b2d-c863-9f97563c1e4c?alt=media&token=b88c20ee-ae78-4529-9480-f3b3b0ad1d45",
        "roleQuestion1": "During my first coop, I was given the challenge of refactoring a continuous integration/deployment pipeline. At the time, I had no experience, and I didn’t even know what those terms meant. I was able to overcome this through a lot of research and testing. I looked into continuous integration frameworks, cloud options for deployment, and containerization tools for our software. After presenting demos to my team, we chose the optimal solution, and I got to work. I containerized apps with Docker and set up a Jenkins server on Azure to manage the pipeline. By the end of my coop, the pipeline was deployed successfully with documentation. I had learned a lot from the experience and improved the company infrastructure greatly by creating a customizable, cheaper CI/CD pipeline.  ",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "During my first coop, I was given the challenge of refactoring a continuous integration/deployment pipeline. At the time, I had no experience, and I didn’t even know what those terms meant. I was able to overcome this through a lot of research and testing. I looked into continuous integration frameworks, cloud options for deployment, and containerization tools for our software. After presenting demos to my team, we chose the optimal solution, and I got to work. I containerized apps with Docker and set up a Jenkins server on Azure to manage the pipeline. By the end of my coop, the pipeline was deployed successfully with documentation. I had learned a lot from the experience and improved the company infrastructure greatly by creating a customizable, cheaper CI/CD pipeline.  "
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551798357367
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "2B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Word of mouth",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "y2333liu@uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Lucy ",
        "lastName": "Liu",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer",
            "Product Manager"
        ],
        "program": "Mechatronics Engineering ",
        "question1": "I want to join Blueprint to have the opportunity to work alongside a group of dedicated developers that are not only passionate about what they do, but most importantly, about the impact they are having through their work. I’ve always held a strong belief that no matter what stage of life I am in, I should make an effort to ensure that I’m making time to help those in need. In our current society, technology is something that surrounds us all; from social media to Google maps, very few can say they live without it. While I feel very fortunate to have a skillset to allow me to contribute to such a booming market, I want to use and develop my skills for social good. Development of technological and soft skills aside, I want to work on a project I know will help make a positive impact on someone’s life and I know that Blueprint will provide me the platform to do that.",
        "question2": "Throughout high-school, I worked with multiple organizations including my church, the local hospital, and a retirement home. At church, I provided piano accompaniment to bi-weekly choir practices and weekly services. At Grand River Hospital, I provided assistance to the hospital for three years by attending a weekly shift to work alongside nurses helping those with kidney issues. My role mainly consisted of transporting patients and aiding them in regular hospital checkups. At the retirement home, I hosted weekly Bingo games on Wednesday nights to senior residents and played board games with them on weekends. \nDuring university, I volunteer at various soup kitchens and shelters depending on what city I am in. Currently, I work with a group called City Eats in San Francisco. We help the homeless in the city by meeting up at the beginning of each month and sometimes bi-monthly to put together over 1000 bagged lunches and distribute them around the city. This is an organization I’ve been very inspired by and feel very passionate about, especially because of the amount of homeless individuals you come across on a daily basis in the city.\n",
        "question3": "A project from the past that I’m really proud of is the Rubik’s Cube Solver. Alongside a couple classmates, we created an autonomous robot using a Lego EV3 kit that could solve any solvable 3 by 3 cube. Due to the restriction of materials we had, the robot only had two motors, one controlling a spinning tray at the bottom to allow change in the orientation of the cube, and another to control the retractable arm that allowed the cube to be flipped and held in place. This project challenged me through mechanical design of the system, and through the development of the algorithm. Before starting, it seemed impossible to develop a program that considered all the possibilities of a cube but through multiple brainstorming sessions, we were successful in creating a working program. Looking back, this project is something I’m proud of not only because it felt amazing the first time we watched the robot solve the cube completely on its own, but also because I learned so much from the project from both a mechanical and software perspective while having a great time with my collaborators.",
        "question4": "While going to the Walt Disney Museum, I learned recently that the voice actors for Mickey and Minnie Mouse actually got married in real life:) ",
        "question5": "I just want to say that even you guys are doing a great job by maintaining such an organized group to make an impact in the community. I've read a lot of the member profiles on Medium and its inspiring how accomplished the team is so keep doing what you're doing! :) ",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I want to join Blueprint to have the opportunity to work alongside a group of dedicated developers that are not only passionate about what they do, but most importantly, about the impact they are having through their work. I’ve always held a strong belief that no matter what stage of life I am in, I should make an effort to ensure that I’m making time to help those in need. In our current society, technology is something that surrounds us all; from social media to Google maps, very few can say they live without it. While I feel very fortunate to have a skillset to allow me to contribute to such a booming market, I want to use and develop my skills for social good. Development of technological and soft skills aside, I want to work on a project I know will help make a positive impact on someone’s life and I know that Blueprint will provide me the platform to do that.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Throughout high-school, I worked with multiple organizations including my church, the local hospital, and a retirement home. At church, I provided piano accompaniment to bi-weekly choir practices and weekly services. At Grand River Hospital, I provided assistance to the hospital for three years by attending a weekly shift to work alongside nurses helping those with kidney issues. My role mainly consisted of transporting patients and aiding them in regular hospital checkups. At the retirement home, I hosted weekly Bingo games on Wednesday nights to senior residents and played board games with them on weekends. \nDuring university, I volunteer at various soup kitchens and shelters depending on what city I am in. Currently, I work with a group called City Eats in San Francisco. We help the homeless in the city by meeting up at the beginning of each month and sometimes bi-monthly to put together over 1000 bagged lunches and distribute them around the city. This is an organization I’ve been very inspired by and feel very passionate about, especially because of the amount of homeless individuals you come across on a daily basis in the city.\n",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "A project from the past that I’m really proud of is the Rubik’s Cube Solver. Alongside a couple classmates, we created an autonomous robot using a Lego EV3 kit that could solve any solvable 3 by 3 cube. Due to the restriction of materials we had, the robot only had two motors, one controlling a spinning tray at the bottom to allow change in the orientation of the cube, and another to control the retractable arm that allowed the cube to be flipped and held in place. This project challenged me through mechanical design of the system, and through the development of the algorithm. Before starting, it seemed impossible to develop a program that considered all the possibilities of a cube but through multiple brainstorming sessions, we were successful in creating a working program. Looking back, this project is something I’m proud of not only because it felt amazing the first time we watched the robot solve the cube completely on its own, but also because I learned so much from the project from both a mechanical and software perspective while having a great time with my collaborators.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "While going to the Walt Disney Museum, I learned recently that the voice actors for Mickey and Minnie Mouse actually got married in real life:) ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I just want to say that even you guys are doing a great job by maintaining such an organized group to make an impact in the community. I've read a lot of the member profiles on Medium and its inspiring how accomplished the team is so keep doing what you're doing! :) ",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\W19-DuringTermUpdate.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F6785fadb-9b02-a24c-2fb3-3d8b929e31ce?alt=media&token=bccd4f36-1095-49fe-91b8-56cd69ee48b2",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F6785fadb-9b02-a24c-2fb3-3d8b929e31ce?alt=media&token=bccd4f36-1095-49fe-91b8-56cd69ee48b2",
        "roleQuestion1": "A technical challenge I faced was recently during work. Normally, to produce waveforms through an AWG, you need to feed in a .txt file. However, my manager told me to produce code to skip the .txt creation and feed information directly. While this is possible, no one at the company has tried doing this before. After days of looking at the programming manual and digging through Google, I realized that I wasn’t getting anywhere. Not wanting to stay blocked, I decided to contacted the AWG company directly, asking for their AWG technician. Finally, after numerous long email exchanges, I was able to overcome my challenge. This taught me to never be afraid to reach out to whoever you might need to help come up with a solution and not limit yourself to just those around you. ",
        "roleQuestion2": "One product I dislike is the HP Spectre x350 15 inch laptops. These computers are a laptop and tablet all in one, with a touchscreen that can fold 360 degrees. While an appealing product at first, and one that I almost bought, there’s an issue with the overall design. At 15 inches, the entire laptop is already large and thick, so to ask the user to fold the screen over for a tablet is not practical, as the result would not make the device very portable or easy to use. This weakens one of the laptop’s main selling points and reduces the validity of the x360 feature. I would reduce the overall size and thickness of the laptop and model it just as a 13 inch laptop. While this might turn away some buyers, it will allow all the HP Spectre’s features to be used to their full advantage",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Product Manager": "One product I dislike is the HP Spectre x350 15 inch laptops. These computers are a laptop and tablet all in one, with a touchscreen that can fold 360 degrees. While an appealing product at first, and one that I almost bought, there’s an issue with the overall design. At 15 inches, the entire laptop is already large and thick, so to ask the user to fold the screen over for a tablet is not practical, as the result would not make the device very portable or easy to use. This weakens one of the laptop’s main selling points and reduces the validity of the x360 feature. I would reduce the overall size and thickness of the laptop and model it just as a 13 inch laptop. While this might turn away some buyers, it will allow all the HP Spectre’s features to be used to their full advantage",
            "Project Developer": "A technical challenge I faced was recently during work. Normally, to produce waveforms through an AWG, you need to feed in a .txt file. However, my manager told me to produce code to skip the .txt creation and feed information directly. While this is possible, no one at the company has tried doing this before. After days of looking at the programming manual and digging through Google, I realized that I wasn’t getting anywhere. Not wanting to stay blocked, I decided to contacted the AWG company directly, asking for their AWG technician. Finally, after numerous long email exchanges, I was able to overcome my challenge. This taught me to never be afraid to reach out to whoever you might need to help come up with a solution and not limit yourself to just those around you. "
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551811737822
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "1B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Co-op",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Co-op"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Facebook",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "sckleung@uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Sam",
        "lastName": "Leung",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer"
        ],
        "program": "Computer Science",
        "question1": "I want to gain hands-on development experience in a collaborative environment with talented people who are all focusing on social good for the sake of social good. I'm always looking to use my free time volunteer in different organizations and at Blueprint, not only would I be working towards helping people, I would also learn useful technical skills to add to my skillset.",
        "question2": "Currently, I'm volunteering at MathSOC as an office manager and at the UW Bike Centre as a general volunteer. I love MathSOC because getting to represent the math faculty to any new and longtime students is something I'm really proud of. In addition to informing students about MathSOC's board games and novelties, I get to tell potential students (from tours) about the math faculty and Waterloo and give back to a community that has taught me so much and allowed me to meet so many talented people. I started volunteering at the bike centre this term because as an avid cyclist, I wanted to learn how a bike is actually made. As a volunteer, I am working on one project bike throughout the term, repairing it to resell for the bike showcase in Spring.\nIn high school, I volunteered as an acoustic guitar performer at a home for seniors. It is one of my favourite volunteer experiences because I got to share my love of music with the seniors; their reactions to our performances made all the rehearsal time worth it.",
        "question3": "At Starterhacks 2019, my team of 5 prototyped an e-commerce Chrome extension called Sift that focused on common items sold online and made a recommendation to the user based on user ratings, reviews, and price. We achieved this through web scraping that involved techniques like sentiment analysis. My part in the project was leading a team of 3 people to build the frontend component of the extension. I'm most proud of this project because I got to apply my knowledge of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to create something that could actually help other people. I got to learn a lot during the process, as I had never built a Chrome extension before. I also got to be in a leader role that also involved me teaching two other people the syntax and concepts behind frontend development, since they were both new to it. By the end of the 48-hour sprint, we were able to present a prototype of our ambitious idea, which was rewarding because it was tangible.",
        "question4": "I can play flute, piano, and guitar (not at the same time)! ",
        "question5": "",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I want to gain hands-on development experience in a collaborative environment with talented people who are all focusing on social good for the sake of social good. I'm always looking to use my free time volunteer in different organizations and at Blueprint, not only would I be working towards helping people, I would also learn useful technical skills to add to my skillset.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Currently, I'm volunteering at MathSOC as an office manager and at the UW Bike Centre as a general volunteer. I love MathSOC because getting to represent the math faculty to any new and longtime students is something I'm really proud of. In addition to informing students about MathSOC's board games and novelties, I get to tell potential students (from tours) about the math faculty and Waterloo and give back to a community that has taught me so much and allowed me to meet so many talented people. I started volunteering at the bike centre this term because as an avid cyclist, I wanted to learn how a bike is actually made. As a volunteer, I am working on one project bike throughout the term, repairing it to resell for the bike showcase in Spring.\nIn high school, I volunteered as an acoustic guitar performer at a home for seniors. It is one of my favourite volunteer experiences because I got to share my love of music with the seniors; their reactions to our performances made all the rehearsal time worth it.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "At Starterhacks 2019, my team of 5 prototyped an e-commerce Chrome extension called Sift that focused on common items sold online and made a recommendation to the user based on user ratings, reviews, and price. We achieved this through web scraping that involved techniques like sentiment analysis. My part in the project was leading a team of 3 people to build the frontend component of the extension. I'm most proud of this project because I got to apply my knowledge of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to create something that could actually help other people. I got to learn a lot during the process, as I had never built a Chrome extension before. I also got to be in a leader role that also involved me teaching two other people the syntax and concepts behind frontend development, since they were both new to it. By the end of the 48-hour sprint, we were able to present a prototype of our ambitious idea, which was rewarding because it was tangible.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I can play flute, piano, and guitar (not at the same time)! ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\Resume12.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fdc48f330-9953-6213-f3a6-27e2212fc3a6?alt=media&token=3e6b5836-9a26-48fa-b4f6-bfb9abb77f34",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fdc48f330-9953-6213-f3a6-27e2212fc3a6?alt=media&token=3e6b5836-9a26-48fa-b4f6-bfb9abb77f34",
        "roleQuestion1": "For my Television Tracker side project, I remember there was a recurring problem involving the Tkinter toolkit. The sort feature in the app had a display issue where if I sorted the list of shows more than once, both sorted lists would appear on the screen, so I focused on the responsible module in my code (I separated different windows by modules). I found  that the first sorted list stayed even after the new one was displayed. So to fix this, at the beginning of my sort function, I cleared the list's contents before displaying the new list of shows. This experience was one of the many during this project that showed me the advantages of modularization not only for readability but for debugging.",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "For my Television Tracker side project, I remember there was a recurring problem involving the Tkinter toolkit. The sort feature in the app had a display issue where if I sorted the list of shows more than once, both sorted lists would appear on the screen, so I focused on the responsible module in my code (I separated different windows by modules). I found  that the first sorted list stayed even after the new one was displayed. So to fix this, at the beginning of my sort function, I cleared the list's contents before displaying the new list of shows. This experience was one of the many during this project that showed me the advantages of modularization not only for readability but for debugging."
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551818097279
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "2A",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Events",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "hdanguye@edu.uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Huy",
        "lastName": "Nguyen",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer"
        ],
        "program": "Computer Science",
        "question1": "I want to join Blueprint because I want to use the skills I learnt as a Computer Science student to help other non-profits in their missions to promote social wellbeing. After volunteering for Frontier College for two terms, I want to take this opportunity as a way not only to keep contributing to the community but also utilise technology to better people’s lives. I also want to develop my communication skills, especially in a team-based setting. My last few times going to hackathons were very valuable to me because not only I help build a meaningful product, but I also start to understand what it is like working with a group of people to achieve a large accomplishment. I hope I can help Blueprint to continue listening to non-profits’ needs and create useful and quality solutions to address those needs.",
        "question2": "For the last two terms I was a volunteer for Frontier College. I was part of the Reading Buddies program and we meet every week at the McCormick Branch Library. Being a “tutor”, I usually pair up with a “buddy” - a primary student – and carry out one-on-one reading sessions with them to develop their reading skills. Usually, I would let my buddy to choose a book in the library and we sit down for 30 minutes going over the book. If the buddy comes to a new vocabulary, I would pronounce them and give the meaning of the word. Afterwards, we spent another 30 minutes playing educational games such as Scrabble Junior. Being a tutor is fun for me as I get to see these children learning something new every week and develop an interest in reading.",
        "question3": "A project that I’m proud of is Parkify. I helped develop it during UofTHacks IV and it is one of the most engaging projects that I have worked with. Fortunately, one of the sponsors (Smartcar) brought a Tesla Model S to the hackathon! Our team is very enthusiastic about being able to get in a Tesla so we decided to use the Smartcar API and use its features to make an app that will help drivers find a parking lot and lot owners manage the cars in under their supervision. I, in particular, is responsible for integrating the API and use Google Firebase to deal with log in and updating data sent by the API. I really enjoyed working on the project because I learnt a lot about using these new features and get to see each team members’ work come together. I especially remember when we got into the Tesla using the API and just spend our time inside celebrating our work.",
        "question4": "I'm really interested in mixology and can make a variety of drinks!",
        "question5": "",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I want to join Blueprint because I want to use the skills I learnt as a Computer Science student to help other non-profits in their missions to promote social wellbeing. After volunteering for Frontier College for two terms, I want to take this opportunity as a way not only to keep contributing to the community but also utilise technology to better people’s lives. I also want to develop my communication skills, especially in a team-based setting. My last few times going to hackathons were very valuable to me because not only I help build a meaningful product, but I also start to understand what it is like working with a group of people to achieve a large accomplishment. I hope I can help Blueprint to continue listening to non-profits’ needs and create useful and quality solutions to address those needs.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "For the last two terms I was a volunteer for Frontier College. I was part of the Reading Buddies program and we meet every week at the McCormick Branch Library. Being a “tutor”, I usually pair up with a “buddy” - a primary student – and carry out one-on-one reading sessions with them to develop their reading skills. Usually, I would let my buddy to choose a book in the library and we sit down for 30 minutes going over the book. If the buddy comes to a new vocabulary, I would pronounce them and give the meaning of the word. Afterwards, we spent another 30 minutes playing educational games such as Scrabble Junior. Being a tutor is fun for me as I get to see these children learning something new every week and develop an interest in reading.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "A project that I’m proud of is Parkify. I helped develop it during UofTHacks IV and it is one of the most engaging projects that I have worked with. Fortunately, one of the sponsors (Smartcar) brought a Tesla Model S to the hackathon! Our team is very enthusiastic about being able to get in a Tesla so we decided to use the Smartcar API and use its features to make an app that will help drivers find a parking lot and lot owners manage the cars in under their supervision. I, in particular, is responsible for integrating the API and use Google Firebase to deal with log in and updating data sent by the API. I really enjoyed working on the project because I learnt a lot about using these new features and get to see each team members’ work come together. I especially remember when we got into the Tesla using the API and just spend our time inside celebrating our work.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I'm really interested in mixology and can make a variety of drinks!",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\my-resume.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F011a81ec-ff0f-efe8-6d5f-4b2237dcf7f5?alt=media&token=7469e021-5468-4f41-9d2b-3e7e6b4b1915",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F011a81ec-ff0f-efe8-6d5f-4b2237dcf7f5?alt=media&token=7469e021-5468-4f41-9d2b-3e7e6b4b1915",
        "roleQuestion1": "A technical problem that I faced also happens when I was working on Parkify. I was following the Firebase tutorial about retrieving and authorising login credentials from the user. However, I could not get the login to work even though I followed the tutorial perfectly. I started to go through online forums but can’t find a question that address my problem. I even looked at the code that I wrote at the last hackathon to see find a difference. Luckily, a Google employee was there so I went to him and asked him about the problem after two hours of frustration. He teaches me how to see error messages in the browser and it turns out the login credentials are not sent properly because of <form> tags in the webapp. After removing those tags, the whole login works properly again.",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "A technical problem that I faced also happens when I was working on Parkify. I was following the Firebase tutorial about retrieving and authorising login credentials from the user. However, I could not get the login to work even though I followed the tutorial perfectly. I started to go through online forums but can’t find a question that address my problem. I even looked at the code that I wrote at the last hackathon to see find a difference. Luckily, a Google employee was there so I went to him and asked him about the problem after two hours of frustration. He teaches me how to see error messages in the browser and it turns out the login credentials are not sent properly because of <form> tags in the webapp. After removing those tags, the whole login works properly again."
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551822602841
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "1B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Other",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "nsubramo@uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Narayan",
        "lastName": "Subramoniam",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer",
            "VP Internal"
        ],
        "program": "Mathematics and Business Administration Double Degree",
        "question1": "I want to join Blueprint because I know it will be the perfect environment for me to involve myself in impactful things. I have heard so much about its amazing culture of collaboration and involvement from friends. I specifically want a platform that will help me improve my technical skills through positively impacting the community. My current long term plans are to contribute to the improvement of systems—starting with the UWaterloo Food Bank. The UW Food Bank is an amazing organization filled with passionate individuals who want to alleviate the stress of food insecurity. However, they are currently using proprietary, and in my personal opinion, inefficient systems for tracking members and resources. I would like to use my time at Blueprint to gain a deeper understanding of the problem and implement an easier and more-accessible system. ",
        "question2": "UWaterloo Food Bank – I am currently a volunteer at the UWaterloo Food Bank where I have never missed my weekly shift. My contributions include professionally dealing with food bank members, inventory management, and store up-keep. It was during my shifts that I realized the time lost in members having to use Google Forms every single time to track their monthly allowances for food. I enjoy the aspect of working on the ground with my community and plan on always contributing my time to the Food Bank.\nSt. Paul’s Student Coffee Shop – I am very proud to volunteer at a student-run coffeeshop on campus that has the best coffee in the world. Located in St. Paul’s college, I volunteer one hour of time every week to manage the shop. The main aspiration of the coffee shop is to support women-grown coffee in developing countries by selling and distributing coffee ethically sourced from there. To help meet that end, I am a part of the business development team where I am currently analyzing the financials of university coffee shops.",
        "question3": "I am most proud of my recent achievements in WATOnomous as sponsorship lead. WATOnomous is UW’s largest student design team focused on creating a fully autonomous vehicle for the purpose of winning an international competition that tests its ability. My role is to lead a team which ensures that WATO has a constant and reliable source of sponsorship funds. Recently, we had to apply to three different endowment funds with varying requirements—all within the first 2 weeks of joining the team. I am very proud of the high level of time management  and comprehensiveness that the entire team exhibited in creating and submitting the 3 applications and 2 presentations. \nI gained the technical skills of using techniques like Pivot tables and macros in Excel that helped sort out the information of around ~300 members, and 4 semesters worth of financial data.",
        "question4": "I recently learned to prepare eggs in 10 different ways! This came as a challenge from my sister who didn’t believe that I could cook eggs more than 3 ways—and still be able to eat it—given that cooking is not currently a skill I have.",
        "question5": "I sincerely, genuinely believe that the existence of Blueprint is in itself AMAZING. The fact that we, as undergraduate students, even have the opportunity to do so much good is beautiful. Thank you so much for the work you put in!",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I want to join Blueprint because I know it will be the perfect environment for me to involve myself in impactful things. I have heard so much about its amazing culture of collaboration and involvement from friends. I specifically want a platform that will help me improve my technical skills through positively impacting the community. My current long term plans are to contribute to the improvement of systems—starting with the UWaterloo Food Bank. The UW Food Bank is an amazing organization filled with passionate individuals who want to alleviate the stress of food insecurity. However, they are currently using proprietary, and in my personal opinion, inefficient systems for tracking members and resources. I would like to use my time at Blueprint to gain a deeper understanding of the problem and implement an easier and more-accessible system. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "UWaterloo Food Bank – I am currently a volunteer at the UWaterloo Food Bank where I have never missed my weekly shift. My contributions include professionally dealing with food bank members, inventory management, and store up-keep. It was during my shifts that I realized the time lost in members having to use Google Forms every single time to track their monthly allowances for food. I enjoy the aspect of working on the ground with my community and plan on always contributing my time to the Food Bank.\nSt. Paul’s Student Coffee Shop – I am very proud to volunteer at a student-run coffeeshop on campus that has the best coffee in the world. Located in St. Paul’s college, I volunteer one hour of time every week to manage the shop. The main aspiration of the coffee shop is to support women-grown coffee in developing countries by selling and distributing coffee ethically sourced from there. To help meet that end, I am a part of the business development team where I am currently analyzing the financials of university coffee shops.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I am most proud of my recent achievements in WATOnomous as sponsorship lead. WATOnomous is UW’s largest student design team focused on creating a fully autonomous vehicle for the purpose of winning an international competition that tests its ability. My role is to lead a team which ensures that WATO has a constant and reliable source of sponsorship funds. Recently, we had to apply to three different endowment funds with varying requirements—all within the first 2 weeks of joining the team. I am very proud of the high level of time management  and comprehensiveness that the entire team exhibited in creating and submitting the 3 applications and 2 presentations. \nI gained the technical skills of using techniques like Pivot tables and macros in Excel that helped sort out the information of around ~300 members, and 4 semesters worth of financial data.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I recently learned to prepare eggs in 10 different ways! This came as a challenge from my sister who didn’t believe that I could cook eggs more than 3 ways—and still be able to eat it—given that cooking is not currently a skill I have.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I sincerely, genuinely believe that the existence of Blueprint is in itself AMAZING. The fact that we, as undergraduate students, even have the opportunity to do so much good is beautiful. Thank you so much for the work you put in!",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\UW_Blueprint_Resume.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F67901a01-c4fa-8a2b-a472-a4439dc204fd?alt=media&token=207b615a-aaca-433b-a61a-c4394e4605e5",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F67901a01-c4fa-8a2b-a472-a4439dc204fd?alt=media&token=207b615a-aaca-433b-a61a-c4394e4605e5",
        "roleQuestion1": "As a Math student I did not have to take CS 135/136, but I did because of the rich learning experience I could get. I was exposed—for the first time—to the concept of functional programming through a Lisp-related language called Racket in this course. One of the assignments we had to complete in this class was to “paint” a picture given a sequence of shapes, with their sizes. I was facing difficulty drawing unique shapes onto the “canvas” as the program recursively ran through user inputs. After the first few hours of working on the assignment over the course of two days, I decided to change my strategy. I started to code on paper and read aloud each step of what I wanted the program to do. After a few hours of doing this, I was finally able to solve the problem!",
        "roleQuestion2": "The ideal organization culture would emphasise three concepts: kindness, dealing with mistakes as situations to create better systems, and having a growth mindset. \nKindness, because there are just too many examples of tech organizations being “corporate”. What I mean by this is that collaboration between groups—although encouraged on paper—is not actively supported by systems in place. E.g. I would like to see introductory UI sessions open to anyone, with highly visible marketing.\nDealing with mistakes maturely follows directly from having a growth mindset. The concept that the skill set you have is completely mutable, and very much open to improvement. I believe that consistent positioning of the idea of persistent effort would help drive this idea home.",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "As a Math student I did not have to take CS 135/136, but I did because of the rich learning experience I could get. I was exposed—for the first time—to the concept of functional programming through a Lisp-related language called Racket in this course. One of the assignments we had to complete in this class was to “paint” a picture given a sequence of shapes, with their sizes. I was facing difficulty drawing unique shapes onto the “canvas” as the program recursively ran through user inputs. After the first few hours of working on the assignment over the course of two days, I decided to change my strategy. I started to code on paper and read aloud each step of what I wanted the program to do. After a few hours of doing this, I was finally able to solve the problem!",
            "VP Internal": "The ideal organization culture would emphasise three concepts: kindness, dealing with mistakes as situations to create better systems, and having a growth mindset. \nKindness, because there are just too many examples of tech organizations being “corporate”. What I mean by this is that collaboration between groups—although encouraged on paper—is not actively supported by systems in place. E.g. I would like to see introductory UI sessions open to anyone, with highly visible marketing.\nDealing with mistakes maturely follows directly from having a growth mindset. The concept that the skill set you have is completely mutable, and very much open to improvement. I believe that consistent positioning of the idea of persistent effort would help drive this idea home."
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551834540517
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "4A",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Facebook",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "alxiao@edu.uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Annie",
        "lastName": "Xiao",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer",
            "Project Lead"
        ],
        "program": "Computer Science",
        "question1": "The reason why I want to join UW Blueprint is simple and probably the most common answer to this question. I just want to help out with projects that were built for social good while gaining practical experience in software development. Although I've gained some experience during co-ops, I'm looking for more rewarding opportunities and projects which I think UW Blueprint can provide me with.",
        "question2": "I can't say that I've contributed much to any non-for-profit organization, but I'm looking for the opportunity to do so. Joining UW Blueprint would be a great way for me to help out the community and get involved with more projects for social good.",
        "question3": "I recently participated in a hackathon where my team and I won for best technical hack. We built a web application to help kids learn about circuits. Our web application would give incomplete pictures of a circuit and the kids would have to draw in the missing part. We used Microsoft's Custom Vision API to train a model to recognize whether the drawing was right or wrong. The web application was built in Node.js in the backend to communicate with the Custom Vision API, and React for an interactive user interface. The whole project was built within 24 hours. ",
        "question4": "Snails can sleep for up to 3 years!",
        "question5": "I think my industry experience in full-stack web development would be a great asset to the team. I thrive in learning new tools and technology, I love working with others to build cool things, and I strive for rigorous code reviews.",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "The reason why I want to join UW Blueprint is simple and probably the most common answer to this question. I just want to help out with projects that were built for social good while gaining practical experience in software development. Although I've gained some experience during co-ops, I'm looking for more rewarding opportunities and projects which I think UW Blueprint can provide me with.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I can't say that I've contributed much to any non-for-profit organization, but I'm looking for the opportunity to do so. Joining UW Blueprint would be a great way for me to help out the community and get involved with more projects for social good.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I recently participated in a hackathon where my team and I won for best technical hack. We built a web application to help kids learn about circuits. Our web application would give incomplete pictures of a circuit and the kids would have to draw in the missing part. We used Microsoft's Custom Vision API to train a model to recognize whether the drawing was right or wrong. The web application was built in Node.js in the backend to communicate with the Custom Vision API, and React for an interactive user interface. The whole project was built within 24 hours. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Snails can sleep for up to 3 years!",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I think my industry experience in full-stack web development would be a great asset to the team. I thrive in learning new tools and technology, I love working with others to build cool things, and I strive for rigorous code reviews.",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\CV-2019.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fba698075-0a9f-39df-9628-59296c91fd65?alt=media&token=8f9ee943-9257-4da2-85e3-74c8ccad2936",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fba698075-0a9f-39df-9628-59296c91fd65?alt=media&token=8f9ee943-9257-4da2-85e3-74c8ccad2936",
        "roleQuestion1": "Bridging tools and technology together is a technical challenge I often find myself faced with. For example, I was working on a project where I wanted to build a mobile app using React Native for the front-end and Node.js for the back-end. Typically, there are libraries that enable a bridge between the two frameworks, however, I just couldn't get the two to communicate with each other. As a software developer, we are constantly evaluating trade-offs and are repeatedly faced with decisions on what tools to use. In this case, the project was extremely time sensitive so I had decided to settle to build a web application in React instead of a mobile app in React Native because it did not lose the interactivity I wanted in the user interface and was easier to implement. ",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "Bridging tools and technology together is a technical challenge I often find myself faced with. For example, I was working on a project where I wanted to build a mobile app using React Native for the front-end and Node.js for the back-end. Typically, there are libraries that enable a bridge between the two frameworks, however, I just couldn't get the two to communicate with each other. As a software developer, we are constantly evaluating trade-offs and are repeatedly faced with decisions on what tools to use. In this case, the project was extremely time sensitive so I had decided to settle to build a web application in React instead of a mobile app in React Native because it did not lose the interactivity I wanted in the user interface and was easier to implement. "
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551842686196
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "2A",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Word of mouth",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "h445chen@edu.uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Huini",
        "lastName": "Chen",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer"
        ],
        "program": "Computer Science",
        "question1": "At my current co-op, I volunteered to be on a team that was dedicated specifically to helping a local Toronto non-for-profit organization, Youthline, redesign their online chatting interface. I found participating in this team to be really rewarding emotionally because I got to contribute to a project that had the potential to improve the experience of many teens seeking help in possibly crucial moments. Blueprint seems like a great organization where I can continue to experience those sparks of joy and really make an impact which makes me very excited!!",
        "question2": "Back in high school I volunteered at Big Brother Big Sisters of Halton and mentored children in grades 1-8 with their studies in various subjects for 2 years. After coming to University, I volunteered at the UW Bike Center for a term assisting people with their bike repairs and handling transactions. My most recent experience comes from Math Orientation 2018 where I was a leader and got to cheer on first years and give them advice on how to adjust to their new surroundings. Furthermore, I became a MOD for Math Orientation 2019. As a MOD my responsibilities are to design the new logos for orientation and create a promotional video using the Adobe suite with the rest of the MOD team.\n",
        "question3": "Last year I went to Equithon and teamed up with 3 other strangers to create a chatbot for women seeking shelters using React and Google Maps API. The chatbot was suppose to be able to anonymously provide answers to frequently asked questions and in addition, be able to direct women to nearby shelters that had open spaces. I am proud of this project because it was the first time I managed to contribute to something that targeted a real issue in the world; one of our teammates used to volunteer at a women’s shelter so this idea came from what she thought would have helped the residents at the shelter. In addition, this project was also a technical milestone for me! It was the first application I programmed in React which opened up the door to the wonderful world of single paged applications.",
        "question4": "https://portage.ca/en/blog/better-understanding-addiction/\n\nAn interesting read!\n",
        "question5": "I discovered this application too late so I didn't have time to update my resume. I'm currently working at Rangle.io as a software developer and is on an IoT project that uses Angular to display information on the availability of a room based on data coming from Phillip Hue sensors that we receive in our NodeJS server. ",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "At my current co-op, I volunteered to be on a team that was dedicated specifically to helping a local Toronto non-for-profit organization, Youthline, redesign their online chatting interface. I found participating in this team to be really rewarding emotionally because I got to contribute to a project that had the potential to improve the experience of many teens seeking help in possibly crucial moments. Blueprint seems like a great organization where I can continue to experience those sparks of joy and really make an impact which makes me very excited!!",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Back in high school I volunteered at Big Brother Big Sisters of Halton and mentored children in grades 1-8 with their studies in various subjects for 2 years. After coming to University, I volunteered at the UW Bike Center for a term assisting people with their bike repairs and handling transactions. My most recent experience comes from Math Orientation 2018 where I was a leader and got to cheer on first years and give them advice on how to adjust to their new surroundings. Furthermore, I became a MOD for Math Orientation 2019. As a MOD my responsibilities are to design the new logos for orientation and create a promotional video using the Adobe suite with the rest of the MOD team.\n",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Last year I went to Equithon and teamed up with 3 other strangers to create a chatbot for women seeking shelters using React and Google Maps API. The chatbot was suppose to be able to anonymously provide answers to frequently asked questions and in addition, be able to direct women to nearby shelters that had open spaces. I am proud of this project because it was the first time I managed to contribute to something that targeted a real issue in the world; one of our teammates used to volunteer at a women’s shelter so this idea came from what she thought would have helped the residents at the shelter. In addition, this project was also a technical milestone for me! It was the first application I programmed in React which opened up the door to the wonderful world of single paged applications.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "https://portage.ca/en/blog/better-understanding-addiction/\n\nAn interesting read!\n",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I discovered this application too late so I didn't have time to update my resume. I'm currently working at Rangle.io as a software developer and is on an IoT project that uses Angular to display information on the availability of a room based on data coming from Phillip Hue sensors that we receive in our NodeJS server. ",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\WaterlooResume.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F56014c78-2929-4cac-efcf-6a3e483a2562?alt=media&token=0644aaf7-0caf-476a-9c3e-44beda44c826",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F56014c78-2929-4cac-efcf-6a3e483a2562?alt=media&token=0644aaf7-0caf-476a-9c3e-44beda44c826",
        "roleQuestion1": "At the start of my work term, I was assigned to a project that used Angular and NodeJS. I knew little about either technologies but was given a ticket to convert HTML tables to Angular Material tables within 3 days. I first looked at the codebase of the project and tried to see if I could understand how the data interacted with the component I was concerned about. I made notes about what confused me and seeked assistance from other developers working on the project. In addition, I read the Angular Material documentation while googling specific code blurbs that confused me and watching videos on how to use Angular Material. All of this led me to finishing the ticket slightly earlier than expected which made me really happy!",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "At the start of my work term, I was assigned to a project that used Angular and NodeJS. I knew little about either technologies but was given a ticket to convert HTML tables to Angular Material tables within 3 days. I first looked at the codebase of the project and tried to see if I could understand how the data interacted with the component I was concerned about. I made notes about what confused me and seeked assistance from other developers working on the project. In addition, I read the Angular Material documentation while googling specific code blurbs that confused me and watching videos on how to use Angular Material. All of this led me to finishing the ticket slightly earlier than expected which made me really happy!"
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551842721426
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "2B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Word of mouth",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "davidchi8666@gmail.com",
        "firstName": "David",
        "lastName": "Chi",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer"
        ],
        "program": "Computer Science",
        "question1": "Since Blueprint is a student run tech development group, it'll be a great opportunity to meet and collaborate with many amazing developers. It'll also be a great learning opportunity to develop a variety of technologies for non-profit organizations. ",
        "question2": "I am currently working for OICR, which is a non-profit organization that works with beginning startups called \"labs\" that are conducting cancer research. I work on the web development team that provides user-friendly websites for the individual \"labs\" promoting the team, and their research and goals. In addition, we collaborate with FACIT to create websites that promote small research groups in hopes of drawing in investments so the groups can be commercialized.",
        "question3": "I've recently worked on a Java-based game. It draws inspiration Pac-Man in which the player runs around a map picks-up dots while avoiding enemies. In my version, the player, the enemies, and the dots have various states. I've implemented various design patterns to handle situations (i.e. visitor design pattern for collision logic, factory design pattern for generating enemies, model view controller for GUI). I am proud to have incorporated things that I've learned from previous courses.",
        "question4": "I am a black belt in Taekwondo and I regularly attend training sessions with a few friends from school.",
        "question5": "",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "Since Blueprint is a student run tech development group, it'll be a great opportunity to meet and collaborate with many amazing developers. It'll also be a great learning opportunity to develop a variety of technologies for non-profit organizations. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I am currently working for OICR, which is a non-profit organization that works with beginning startups called \"labs\" that are conducting cancer research. I work on the web development team that provides user-friendly websites for the individual \"labs\" promoting the team, and their research and goals. In addition, we collaborate with FACIT to create websites that promote small research groups in hopes of drawing in investments so the groups can be commercialized.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I've recently worked on a Java-based game. It draws inspiration Pac-Man in which the player runs around a map picks-up dots while avoiding enemies. In my version, the player, the enemies, and the dots have various states. I've implemented various design patterns to handle situations (i.e. visitor design pattern for collision logic, factory design pattern for generating enemies, model view controller for GUI). I am proud to have incorporated things that I've learned from previous courses.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I am a black belt in Taekwondo and I regularly attend training sessions with a few friends from school.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\Resume 1.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fa596adf8-ad08-22cf-9013-c6b2bb8072c2?alt=media&token=5534be08-915f-47ed-9f6d-7f8a7e4bcd81",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fa596adf8-ad08-22cf-9013-c6b2bb8072c2?alt=media&token=5534be08-915f-47ed-9f6d-7f8a7e4bcd81",
        "roleQuestion1": "During a hackathon I've previously attended, my group attempted to incorporate a specific API. The technical challenge was that we never used the API before and had to quickly familiarize ourselves with it. I read the documentation as well as a few tutorials to learn the basics, then I attempted to perform basic functionalities using the API. After trying to implement more advanced functionalities, I've ran across a few errors. I attempted to solve this on my own for a bit before asking one of my teammates to look over my code. Afterwards, we pair programmed together as we found it more efficient because one of us may know something the other doesn't. In the end, our project was successful and we were able to demo for the judges.",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "During a hackathon I've previously attended, my group attempted to incorporate a specific API. The technical challenge was that we never used the API before and had to quickly familiarize ourselves with it. I read the documentation as well as a few tutorials to learn the basics, then I attempted to perform basic functionalities using the API. After trying to implement more advanced functionalities, I've ran across a few errors. I attempted to solve this on my own for a bit before asking one of my teammates to look over my code. Afterwards, we pair programmed together as we found it more efficient because one of us may know something the other doesn't. In the end, our project was successful and we were able to demo for the judges."
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551844429495
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "3A",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Co-op",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Co-op"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Facebook",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "tfwong@edu.uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Alvin",
        "lastName": "Wong",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer"
        ],
        "program": "Computer Engineering",
        "question1": "I am eager to be a part of the UW Blueprint team because I genuinely enjoy exploring the potential of technology and challenging myself to approach new and unfamiliar projects. I see this opportunity as a valuable experience for me to apply my skills in a non-academic setting, and at the same time gaining more knowledge on a variety of topics not only by working with a group of dedicated students, but with the cooperating organizations with a large diversity of background and expertise. I particularly appreciate the element of real-life application because nothing else will be more rewarding than creating a product that would actually be helpful to the community. I personally believe that the use of technology shall not be limited to certain groups in the population due to field of education and social status, and I was very excited that the team aims to build open resources for the public as it allows the sharing of skills and aids the growth of non-profit organizations through improving their methods of promotion and communication.",
        "question2": "With a HIGH FIVE certification, I volunteered as a summer day camp counselor for the City of Markham. My responsibility was to participate in organizing events. Such events include activities like socials, water games, etc. It was my responsibility to help ensure day camps run smoothly and everyone had a good time. The challenge I face was that I had to deal with different age groups of youth. Each age group behaved differently, and it required different methods to communicate with them. Not all activities were suitable for all age. It was a challenge to organize different activities specific to age groups, as well as communicating with them with patience. I took pride in this experience because it had a meaning to me in being able to positively impact the youth's growth by providing a happy summer. I have learned communication skills and the hard work behind organizing events. ",
        "question3": "The project I am the most proud of is The Lemon Law. It was a chat application me and my teammates developed over EngHacks 2017, and it was rated one of the top 10 projects that year. The application was designed to place two random individuals of opposite genders into a chat room for 5 minutes. This idea was inspired by “The Lemon Law” from the show How I Met Your Mother, which describes a person who is allowed to terminate a date in the first 5 minutes without hard feelings. The construction of this application was based on the commonly used dating websites and communication applications like Facebook and Whatsapp. ",
        "question4": "I am determined to try all bubble tea in the world.",
        "question5": "",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I am eager to be a part of the UW Blueprint team because I genuinely enjoy exploring the potential of technology and challenging myself to approach new and unfamiliar projects. I see this opportunity as a valuable experience for me to apply my skills in a non-academic setting, and at the same time gaining more knowledge on a variety of topics not only by working with a group of dedicated students, but with the cooperating organizations with a large diversity of background and expertise. I particularly appreciate the element of real-life application because nothing else will be more rewarding than creating a product that would actually be helpful to the community. I personally believe that the use of technology shall not be limited to certain groups in the population due to field of education and social status, and I was very excited that the team aims to build open resources for the public as it allows the sharing of skills and aids the growth of non-profit organizations through improving their methods of promotion and communication.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "With a HIGH FIVE certification, I volunteered as a summer day camp counselor for the City of Markham. My responsibility was to participate in organizing events. Such events include activities like socials, water games, etc. It was my responsibility to help ensure day camps run smoothly and everyone had a good time. The challenge I face was that I had to deal with different age groups of youth. Each age group behaved differently, and it required different methods to communicate with them. Not all activities were suitable for all age. It was a challenge to organize different activities specific to age groups, as well as communicating with them with patience. I took pride in this experience because it had a meaning to me in being able to positively impact the youth's growth by providing a happy summer. I have learned communication skills and the hard work behind organizing events. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "The project I am the most proud of is The Lemon Law. It was a chat application me and my teammates developed over EngHacks 2017, and it was rated one of the top 10 projects that year. The application was designed to place two random individuals of opposite genders into a chat room for 5 minutes. This idea was inspired by “The Lemon Law” from the show How I Met Your Mother, which describes a person who is allowed to terminate a date in the first 5 minutes without hard feelings. The construction of this application was based on the commonly used dating websites and communication applications like Facebook and Whatsapp. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I am determined to try all bubble tea in the world.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\blueprint_resume.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F31571097-f3bd-d7a3-708e-cba1249801d9?alt=media&token=a2aa3654-9031-4eaf-8741-f10a4e99af48",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F31571097-f3bd-d7a3-708e-cba1249801d9?alt=media&token=a2aa3654-9031-4eaf-8741-f10a4e99af48",
        "roleQuestion1": "I was assigned to build features on an API in previous company. The technical challenge I faced was that I had no idea how to build that feature and I was not familiar with the technology used. First, I start by familiarizing myself with technology through online resources, such as tutorials and blogs. When I started building the features, I usually try to solve any challenge I face before I ask for help. I also love to collaborate with team members so that I can provide my input regarding the features and they can provide me feedback or advice. I work on my problem step by step, collaborating with team members along the way. I believe technology can be used in many ways, and collaborating is the best way to explore all possibilities, preparing myself for future problems.",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "I was assigned to build features on an API in previous company. The technical challenge I faced was that I had no idea how to build that feature and I was not familiar with the technology used. First, I start by familiarizing myself with technology through online resources, such as tutorials and blogs. When I started building the features, I usually try to solve any challenge I face before I ask for help. I also love to collaborate with team members so that I can provide my input regarding the features and they can provide me feedback or advice. I work on my problem step by step, collaborating with team members along the way. I believe technology can be used in many ways, and collaborating is the best way to explore all possibilities, preparing myself for future problems."
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551844875739
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "3A",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Facebook",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "y22xin@edu.uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Karolina",
        "lastName": "Xin",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer"
        ],
        "program": "Computer Science",
        "question1": "It would be an absolute honour to be able to work alongside such a passionate team of hardworking people, who are all eager to do social good through the powers of technology. One of the main reasons on why I got into technology was so that I could find ways to harness my skills in order to help those around me. It is the reason why my multitude of hackathon projects all revolve around making something that would benefit my community, ranging from mental health awareness, all the way to connecting homeless shelters with restaurants so that perfectly good food doesn’t go to waste. Being able to be a project developer for Blueprint would also allow me to expand my technical skills (ideally in Web development), as well as to be an advocate for nonprofits, and what we as students can do to help them. I would love to learn about all the innovative ideas Blueprint has, and to get inspired by them as well. Furthermore, I know that I will have time to work on Blueprint, and to fully commit myself to the projects next term. ",
        "question2": "I enjoy getting involved at school, as it supports my community, and my schoolmates. Throughout my university career, I have been a part of the Women in CS committee, where I was the publicity director. I got to create posters and advertise events that support a minority, all around campus. In total, I put up about 40 posters per event, and coordinated volunteers. Then as a Microsoft Student Partner, we planned a Microsoft hackathon, Azure day, and attended technical workshops, such as BlockChain. As a Communitech student ambassador, we organized the Code/Design to Win competition at Waterloo. This competition is held across North America, where university students compete to win $5000. We also attended hackathons to promote Communitech. I have also been a First-Year Director in Math Soc. As a director, I led a team of 6 first-year representatives to organize 3 major events for first-years, in order to help with their transition into Waterloo. We had two technical events, and one relaxation event, where we got a huge turnout for both. In addition, I have been a head Pink Tie leader during orientation week, where I got to welcome incoming students, and assure their parents that their children will be taken care of. ",
        "question3": "Reflecting on my various projects, I must say that ‘Hello Good Day’ is my proudest work. At the time, there were too many suicides going on at Waterloo, and my team and I knew we wanted to do something about it. We created a mobile app that allows the user to take pictures of various things around them, and have a motivational saying appear related to something in the picture. For example, if they took a picture of the bright outdoors, it would show a saying like, “Have a sunny day!” We hoped this would allow people to appreciate the small things more, thus resulting in a more positive outlook on life. Another reason that it is my proudest project, was because of how well we worked as a team. We had 24hrs to create this project, while having to learn everything about Google APIs. By splitting up the project, with one working on the Google Vision API, I working on the map feature, and my other teammate working on merging both features together, everyone played a major role. I honestly could not have asked for a better team, and was very proud of all of them. Our hard work, and amazing teamwork paid off, as we built something for a cause that we all strongly believed in.",
        "question4": "I can't lick my elbow, but I can lick YOUR elbow. ;)\n\nI also enjoy vlogging in my spare time (currently still working on improving my videos which is why I haven't really advertised my YouTube channel yet). But if you're curious, my channel is simply Karolina Xin. :) ",
        "question5": "Honestly, Blueprint seems like a lot of fun, and it would be an amazing opportunity to give back to the community using our coding skills. Also, thank you all for your time on reading all the applications :)",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "It would be an absolute honour to be able to work alongside such a passionate team of hardworking people, who are all eager to do social good through the powers of technology. One of the main reasons on why I got into technology was so that I could find ways to harness my skills in order to help those around me. It is the reason why my multitude of hackathon projects all revolve around making something that would benefit my community, ranging from mental health awareness, all the way to connecting homeless shelters with restaurants so that perfectly good food doesn’t go to waste. Being able to be a project developer for Blueprint would also allow me to expand my technical skills (ideally in Web development), as well as to be an advocate for nonprofits, and what we as students can do to help them. I would love to learn about all the innovative ideas Blueprint has, and to get inspired by them as well. Furthermore, I know that I will have time to work on Blueprint, and to fully commit myself to the projects next term. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I enjoy getting involved at school, as it supports my community, and my schoolmates. Throughout my university career, I have been a part of the Women in CS committee, where I was the publicity director. I got to create posters and advertise events that support a minority, all around campus. In total, I put up about 40 posters per event, and coordinated volunteers. Then as a Microsoft Student Partner, we planned a Microsoft hackathon, Azure day, and attended technical workshops, such as BlockChain. As a Communitech student ambassador, we organized the Code/Design to Win competition at Waterloo. This competition is held across North America, where university students compete to win $5000. We also attended hackathons to promote Communitech. I have also been a First-Year Director in Math Soc. As a director, I led a team of 6 first-year representatives to organize 3 major events for first-years, in order to help with their transition into Waterloo. We had two technical events, and one relaxation event, where we got a huge turnout for both. In addition, I have been a head Pink Tie leader during orientation week, where I got to welcome incoming students, and assure their parents that their children will be taken care of. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Reflecting on my various projects, I must say that ‘Hello Good Day’ is my proudest work. At the time, there were too many suicides going on at Waterloo, and my team and I knew we wanted to do something about it. We created a mobile app that allows the user to take pictures of various things around them, and have a motivational saying appear related to something in the picture. For example, if they took a picture of the bright outdoors, it would show a saying like, “Have a sunny day!” We hoped this would allow people to appreciate the small things more, thus resulting in a more positive outlook on life. Another reason that it is my proudest project, was because of how well we worked as a team. We had 24hrs to create this project, while having to learn everything about Google APIs. By splitting up the project, with one working on the Google Vision API, I working on the map feature, and my other teammate working on merging both features together, everyone played a major role. I honestly could not have asked for a better team, and was very proud of all of them. Our hard work, and amazing teamwork paid off, as we built something for a cause that we all strongly believed in.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I can't lick my elbow, but I can lick YOUR elbow. ;)\n\nI also enjoy vlogging in my spare time (currently still working on improving my videos which is why I haven't really advertised my YouTube channel yet). But if you're curious, my channel is simply Karolina Xin. :) ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Honestly, Blueprint seems like a lot of fun, and it would be an amazing opportunity to give back to the community using our coding skills. Also, thank you all for your time on reading all the applications :)",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\KarolinaXin.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F17c14f9b-4194-6314-4b2b-5ef96276e927?alt=media&token=036bd3c8-f275-4b9b-88cd-ff7f0969cba2",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F17c14f9b-4194-6314-4b2b-5ef96276e927?alt=media&token=036bd3c8-f275-4b9b-88cd-ff7f0969cba2",
        "roleQuestion1": "At my most recent co-op, the first task that was given to me, was to create an end-to-end software upgrade wizard, using React. I didn’t know much about React before, nor much about my company’s code base either. My team lead simply gave me a link to a tutorial, and said, “Learn this.” So I did. I made notes throughout the videos, and thought about how to apply it to my code. I explored the code base in order to get a sense on their style of coding, as well as looking for any potential examples. Any outstanding questions, I would make a list of, as I knew that my teammates were busy. I would write out everything that I was doing so that I wouldn’t forget any details. This was especially important, as I had to present it at a demo to our company’s investors. ",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "At my most recent co-op, the first task that was given to me, was to create an end-to-end software upgrade wizard, using React. I didn’t know much about React before, nor much about my company’s code base either. My team lead simply gave me a link to a tutorial, and said, “Learn this.” So I did. I made notes throughout the videos, and thought about how to apply it to my code. I explored the code base in order to get a sense on their style of coding, as well as looking for any potential examples. Any outstanding questions, I would make a list of, as I knew that my teammates were busy. I would write out everything that I was doing so that I wouldn’t forget any details. This was especially important, as I had to present it at a demo to our company’s investors. "
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551849340087
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "1B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Co-op",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Co-op"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Facebook",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "csathish@edu.uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Chandana",
        "lastName": "Sathish",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer"
        ],
        "program": "Software Engineering",
        "question1": "One of the main reasons I joined Software Engineering was to work on the intersection of social impact and technology. In my opinion, technology helps increase the impact of our actions by many folds. I came to this realization only when my lack of technical skills stood as a barrier between me and the positive impact I was trying to create with my non-profit organisation. I feel like Blueprint gives me the perfect platform to work towards my goal of ever increasing the intersection between the two fields of tech and social impact. It gives me a chance to work with organisations that I can empathize with and relate to in order to help them better transform the world in my own small way.",
        "question2": "In India, I spent more than 3 years volunteering for various organisations. During these three years I have volunteered for various organisations like 'The Ugly Indian' and 'Parikrama Humanity Foundation' as well as school run projects like 'empoWer' and 'WhyWaste?'.\n> Parikrama Humanity Foundation:\n  - Mentored 2 students for 3 months from weaker backgrounds to help improve their academics as well as take up a project that have a social aspect to it.\n> empoWer:\n  - Taught (for two years) the support staff at school to read, write and speak English\n  - Taught the support staff to do basic operations using Computers (like use MS Word, access Google) for 6 months\n> WhyWaste?\n  - Convinced more than 15 hotels across Bangalore to employ sustainable practices (recycle, optimize water usage, on-site composting, etc) and went every few weeks for follow-up checks\n\nApart from this I also started my own non-profit organization described in my answer below.",
        "question3": "• Co-founded a non-profit organization called STRIVE tackling environmental challenges on March 24th, 2016\n• Introduced 3 projects (STRIVE Hour, N2N, Youth Mentoring Youth) in different fields of recycling, energy conservation and education\n• Impact:\n - lead a team of over 60 volunteers\n - engaged over 800 families, 5 schools and 9 offices over 2 years\n - saved 13 million Wh of energy and recycled over 18 tonnes of paper\n• Awards and recognition:\n - Ashoka's Innovators for the Public: Ashoka's Youth Venture\n - 3M-CII Young Innovator's Challenge: Semi-Finalists\n - Various magazine and newspaper features\n\nWorking as the Founder/CEO at STRIVE for almost 3 years now has given me adequate skills to see a project from start to finish, put myself in multiple roles and perform the required tasks and work with and handle teams both large and small. It has opened my perspective on various topics by many folds and helped me think in the most unconventional way. But most importantly, it has taught me the satisfaction you get from bringing a smile to someone's face or hearing from people about how your actions are impacting them in a positive way is unmatched and one that you can never get from any other line of work. ",
        "question4": "I accidentally butt dialed 911 once. Since my phone was on silent, I didn't notice or return their calls. So a few minutes later, a cop showed up to my lecture (in front of my whole cohort (rip)) asking for me.\n\nGuess who had to change some settings on her phone after that day...",
        "question5": "",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "One of the main reasons I joined Software Engineering was to work on the intersection of social impact and technology. In my opinion, technology helps increase the impact of our actions by many folds. I came to this realization only when my lack of technical skills stood as a barrier between me and the positive impact I was trying to create with my non-profit organisation. I feel like Blueprint gives me the perfect platform to work towards my goal of ever increasing the intersection between the two fields of tech and social impact. It gives me a chance to work with organisations that I can empathize with and relate to in order to help them better transform the world in my own small way.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "In India, I spent more than 3 years volunteering for various organisations. During these three years I have volunteered for various organisations like 'The Ugly Indian' and 'Parikrama Humanity Foundation' as well as school run projects like 'empoWer' and 'WhyWaste?'.\n> Parikrama Humanity Foundation:\n  - Mentored 2 students for 3 months from weaker backgrounds to help improve their academics as well as take up a project that have a social aspect to it.\n> empoWer:\n  - Taught (for two years) the support staff at school to read, write and speak English\n  - Taught the support staff to do basic operations using Computers (like use MS Word, access Google) for 6 months\n> WhyWaste?\n  - Convinced more than 15 hotels across Bangalore to employ sustainable practices (recycle, optimize water usage, on-site composting, etc) and went every few weeks for follow-up checks\n\nApart from this I also started my own non-profit organization described in my answer below.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "• Co-founded a non-profit organization called STRIVE tackling environmental challenges on March 24th, 2016\n• Introduced 3 projects (STRIVE Hour, N2N, Youth Mentoring Youth) in different fields of recycling, energy conservation and education\n• Impact:\n - lead a team of over 60 volunteers\n - engaged over 800 families, 5 schools and 9 offices over 2 years\n - saved 13 million Wh of energy and recycled over 18 tonnes of paper\n• Awards and recognition:\n - Ashoka's Innovators for the Public: Ashoka's Youth Venture\n - 3M-CII Young Innovator's Challenge: Semi-Finalists\n - Various magazine and newspaper features\n\nWorking as the Founder/CEO at STRIVE for almost 3 years now has given me adequate skills to see a project from start to finish, put myself in multiple roles and perform the required tasks and work with and handle teams both large and small. It has opened my perspective on various topics by many folds and helped me think in the most unconventional way. But most importantly, it has taught me the satisfaction you get from bringing a smile to someone's face or hearing from people about how your actions are impacting them in a positive way is unmatched and one that you can never get from any other line of work. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I accidentally butt dialed 911 once. Since my phone was on silent, I didn't notice or return their calls. So a few minutes later, a cop showed up to my lecture (in front of my whole cohort (rip)) asking for me.\n\nGuess who had to change some settings on her phone after that day...",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\20762088-Resume.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fe631b79f-2b29-6426-aa8d-201be7babe02?alt=media&token=c3c98091-7919-4e90-b437-43b63b01248a",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2Fe631b79f-2b29-6426-aa8d-201be7babe02?alt=media&token=c3c98091-7919-4e90-b437-43b63b01248a",
        "roleQuestion1": "One of the main technical challenges I faced early on was continuing from where I left off my code. I used to find it hard to think about my previous logic and continue my work using the same one since I used to work over a code over days for short time periods.\nThe solution to this might sound very intuitive and obvious right now, but it was not at the time to me. As a way to over come this, I started having code goals rather than time limits. By this I mean I divided my work into different aspects of the code and every time I sat down to work on it, I would only stop once I was able to finish off that chunk. Moreover, commenting my code my efficiently and naming my variables in a way that I could recollect my logic more easily helped me overcome this issue easily.",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "One of the main technical challenges I faced early on was continuing from where I left off my code. I used to find it hard to think about my previous logic and continue my work using the same one since I used to work over a code over days for short time periods.\nThe solution to this might sound very intuitive and obvious right now, but it was not at the time to me. As a way to over come this, I started having code goals rather than time limits. By this I mean I divided my work into different aspects of the code and every time I sat down to work on it, I would only stop once I was able to finish off that chunk. Moreover, commenting my code my efficiently and naming my variables in a way that I could recollect my logic more easily helped me overcome this issue easily."
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551852646806
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "3B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Co-op",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Co-op"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Facebook",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "ndpark97@gmail.com",
        "firstName": "Andy",
        "lastName": "Park",
        "positions": [
            "Product Designer",
            "Design Director"
        ],
        "program": "Systems Design Engineering",
        "question1": "I want to help make a difference in the world - no matter how small. Blueprint connects various non-profits with different objectives with students to deliver technology services.  Helping these organizations achieve their goals also helps make the world a better place. It would also expose me to various problems that real people face, such as inclusion for people with cognitive disabilities, or plastic pollution in developing countries. It would help me become a better designer.",
        "question2": "I've volunteered with Big Brothers Big Sisters to help kids who are new to Canada integrate to the new environment. I came up with various fun educational activities which led to receiving Volunteer of the Year award. I have also volunteered for the University of Waterloo as a engineering ambassador, leading the Shadow Day program for two years. Lastly, I've worked at Multiple Sclerosis Society of Canada. ",
        "question3": "I'm most proud of the design system that I established at a startup I worked at. Design was relatively new at the company and thus had a huge design debt. I decided to tackle that problem by establishing a design system that would reduce the design debt. I researched design systems, interviewed stakeholders, and created a functional design guide as a starting point. The final result significantly reduced design time, lead to happier designers, and less inconsistencies in the product. ",
        "question4": "I once told an inappropriate joke during an interview, which lead to me receiving an offer for that job. ",
        "question5": "",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I want to help make a difference in the world - no matter how small. Blueprint connects various non-profits with different objectives with students to deliver technology services.  Helping these organizations achieve their goals also helps make the world a better place. It would also expose me to various problems that real people face, such as inclusion for people with cognitive disabilities, or plastic pollution in developing countries. It would help me become a better designer.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I've volunteered with Big Brothers Big Sisters to help kids who are new to Canada integrate to the new environment. I came up with various fun educational activities which led to receiving Volunteer of the Year award. I have also volunteered for the University of Waterloo as a engineering ambassador, leading the Shadow Day program for two years. Lastly, I've worked at Multiple Sclerosis Society of Canada. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I'm most proud of the design system that I established at a startup I worked at. Design was relatively new at the company and thus had a huge design debt. I decided to tackle that problem by establishing a design system that would reduce the design debt. I researched design systems, interviewed stakeholders, and created a functional design guide as a starting point. The final result significantly reduced design time, lead to happier designers, and less inconsistencies in the product. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I once told an inappropriate joke during an interview, which lead to me receiving an offer for that job. ",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\AndyPark_Design.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F5dae6861-0516-a414-0561-436bb9bb4dc4?alt=media&token=f47daae5-8cc8-4cfe-9c50-5b6bb8a732fa",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F5dae6861-0516-a414-0561-436bb9bb4dc4?alt=media&token=f47daae5-8cc8-4cfe-9c50-5b6bb8a732fa",
        "roleQuestion1": "https://www.ndpark.ca/\n",
        "roleQuestion2": "I usually have one-on-ones to learn more about them - how they work, what they like, etc. This helps break down barriers and helps build a personal connection, which usually leads to better teamwork and collaboration. I borrow a lot of how I work with others from Agile methodology, such as having stand-ups and a Kanban board.  Communication, in my opinion, is essential for success. I like to introduce collaborative tools such as Figma because it makes communication more fluid compared to other design tools. ",
        "roleQuestion3": "",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Design Director": "I usually have one-on-ones to learn more about them - how they work, what they like, etc. This helps break down barriers and helps build a personal connection, which usually leads to better teamwork and collaboration. I borrow a lot of how I work with others from Agile methodology, such as having stand-ups and a Kanban board.  Communication, in my opinion, is essential for success. I like to introduce collaborative tools such as Figma because it makes communication more fluid compared to other design tools. ",
            "Product Designer": "https://www.ndpark.ca/\n"
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551853736440
    },
    {
        "academicYear": "3B",
        "binaryQuestion1": "Academic",
        "binaryQuestion2": "Yes",
        "binaryQuestions": [
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Academic"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Co-op"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in an academic (school) term or a co-op term?*",
                "selected": "Academic"
            },
            {
                "binaryOptions": [
                    {
                        "value": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you be in Waterloo during the upcoming term?*",
                "selected": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "dropdownQuestion1": "Word of mouth",
        "dropdownQuestions": [
            {
                "options": [
                    {
                        "value": "Facebook"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Instagram"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Word of mouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Clubs fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Events"
                    },
                    {
                        "value": "Other"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where did you hear about us?*",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ],
        "email": "r5rao@edu.uwaterloo.ca",
        "firstName": "Ritika",
        "lastName": "Rao",
        "positions": [
            "Project Developer",
            "VP Projects",
            "VP Events"
        ],
        "program": "Mathematical Economics, Computer Science Minor",
        "question1": "I love getting involved with clubs and teams on campus, where I can exchange ideas, contribute meaningfully and meet interesting people. Having heard a lot about the culture at Blueprint, I want to join the organization so that I can meet like-minded people with whom I can share my passion for volunteering. I enjoy volunteering greatly, and try to volunteer for causes that I support as much as I can, whenever possible. I feel that joining Blueprint would allow me to combine my love for volunteering with technology, and actually build something relevant in a social space. In addition to this, Blueprint has a supportive team environment and strong mentorship program. Along with being able to contribute to the team, I feel that I will be able to learn a lot from my team members and build meaningful relationships. I resonate strongly with Blueprint’s motto of building technology for social good.",
        "question2": "I have led the Feds Volunteer Centre at UW as its coordinator, and run several successful campaigns and initiatives. My goal was to raise awareness about volunteering around Kitchener-Waterloo and to promote students to volunteer on and off campus. Through the service, I managed to engage students in 2000+ hours of volunteering at an organization of their choice, in the Winter 2018 term. \nAt my high school in Dubai, I participated in the SAATHI initiative, during which my batch-mates and I organized fun events for children with physical disabilities, and attempted to provide them with an interactive and engaging experience. \nI have also spearheaded the PALS initiative at my high school, which was essentially a program to instruct the janitorial and support staff of the school with the basic essentials of English and Mathematics.\nI enjoy devoting time to the local soup kitchen, ‘Food Not Bombs’, where I have cooked and served vegetarian meals to the community.",
        "question3": "As the coordinator of the Feds Volunteer Centre, I spearheaded the first ‘Timeraiser’ initiative at UW to promote volunteerism – it is like a fundraiser, but instead of donating funds, you donate your time towards volunteerism. I saw this project through right from its inception, up until its end. I implemented useful marketing strategies to spread the word about the Timeraiser around campus and got around 250 students to sign up and pledge a minimum number of hours. All Feds services were also participants in the Timeraiser. Throughout the event period, students volunteered at their local organizations and tracked their hours on our online tracker, with the help of our executive team, to meet their pledge goals. To incentivize students to volunteer, prizes were handed out to the top 6 participants who volunteered for the most number of hours. These prizes were provided free of cost by Toronto Maple Leafs, Clif Bars, Skyzone, etc. That month, 2000+ hours of volunteering were recorded in total.",
        "question4": "I can speak 6 languages - English, Hindi, Arabic, French, Spanish and Kannada!",
        "question5": "",
        "questions": [
            {
                "answer": "I love getting involved with clubs and teams on campus, where I can exchange ideas, contribute meaningfully and meet interesting people. Having heard a lot about the culture at Blueprint, I want to join the organization so that I can meet like-minded people with whom I can share my passion for volunteering. I enjoy volunteering greatly, and try to volunteer for causes that I support as much as I can, whenever possible. I feel that joining Blueprint would allow me to combine my love for volunteering with technology, and actually build something relevant in a social space. In addition to this, Blueprint has a supportive team environment and strong mentorship program. Along with being able to contribute to the team, I feel that I will be able to learn a lot from my team members and build meaningful relationships. I resonate strongly with Blueprint’s motto of building technology for social good.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I want to meet awesome people that are passionate about volunteering and helping non-profits!",
                "question": "Why do you want to join Blueprint?*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I have led the Feds Volunteer Centre at UW as its coordinator, and run several successful campaigns and initiatives. My goal was to raise awareness about volunteering around Kitchener-Waterloo and to promote students to volunteer on and off campus. Through the service, I managed to engage students in 2000+ hours of volunteering at an organization of their choice, in the Winter 2018 term. \nAt my high school in Dubai, I participated in the SAATHI initiative, during which my batch-mates and I organized fun events for children with physical disabilities, and attempted to provide them with an interactive and engaging experience. \nI have also spearheaded the PALS initiative at my high school, which was essentially a program to instruct the janitorial and support staff of the school with the basic essentials of English and Mathematics.\nI enjoy devoting time to the local soup kitchen, ‘Food Not Bombs’, where I have cooked and served vegetarian meals to the community.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. Red Cross, local soup kitchen, etc.",
                "question": "Describe your contributions to any volunteer/non-profit organizations:*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "As the coordinator of the Feds Volunteer Centre, I spearheaded the first ‘Timeraiser’ initiative at UW to promote volunteerism – it is like a fundraiser, but instead of donating funds, you donate your time towards volunteerism. I saw this project through right from its inception, up until its end. I implemented useful marketing strategies to spread the word about the Timeraiser around campus and got around 250 students to sign up and pledge a minimum number of hours. All Feds services were also participants in the Timeraiser. Throughout the event period, students volunteered at their local organizations and tracked their hours on our online tracker, with the help of our executive team, to meet their pledge goals. To incentivize students to volunteer, prizes were handed out to the top 6 participants who volunteered for the most number of hours. These prizes were provided free of cost by Toronto Maple Leafs, Clif Bars, Skyzone, etc. That month, 2000+ hours of volunteering were recorded in total.",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I recently worked on a simple website",
                "question": "Tell us about a project you have worked on in the past that you’re most proud of. *"
            },
            {
                "answer": "I can speak 6 languages - English, Hindi, Arabic, French, Spanish and Kannada!",
                "placeholder": "e.g. I can lick my elbow!",
                "question": "Tell us a fun fact!*"
            },
            {
                "answer": "",
                "placeholder": "(Optional)",
                "question": "Is there anything else you would like to share?"
            }
        ],
        "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\Ritika Rao.pdf",
        "resumeInput": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F3646695d-aa69-6cb7-44c6-b41d8ae1ab4f?alt=media&token=1a0cb2eb-2df4-4022-a6de-c799a85e14ce",
        "resumeUrl": "https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/uw-blueprint.appspot.com/o/resumes%2F3646695d-aa69-6cb7-44c6-b41d8ae1ab4f?alt=media&token=1a0cb2eb-2df4-4022-a6de-c799a85e14ce",
        "roleQuestion1": "I have always been comfortable with coding in Java, C++, Python, etc. However, I struggled with front-end development because I found it slightly monotonous. This proved to be a hindrance when I wanted to build my own website. My only option was to actually sit down and learn how to code with HTML and CSS. Thus, I began doing online courses to familiarize myself with the web-building tools. Even after taking these courses, I could not build my website perfectly. Finally, I began working with friends and mentors on web development side-projects so that I could get actual hands-on experience with front-end development. This is when I actually got the hang of coding in HTML and CSS. I even worked on simple projects of my own in order to test my capabilities.",
        "roleQuestion2": "",
        "roleQuestion3": "At a science fair organized by my school classmates and I for 1000 students, there was a major issue of task delegation. Students on the organizing team did not come forward to pick particular tasks for themselves; instead, they just tried to help with general tasks. Hence, when issues relating to particular tasks arose, no one took ownership of those issues. I created a chart based on skillset and incomplete tasks, and assigned tasks to each student based on what matched their skills. They were expected to report to their task manager each day with updates, and these updates were added to the chart. The chart was also used to track the expected time for task completion against the time being spent on the task (task progress). Thus, tasks were completed more smoothly.",
        "roleQuestion4": "",
        "roleQuestion5": "I like to prioritize my time based on the urgency of the task – I rank my tasks in order of what needs to be completed first and what can be completed subsequently. I also like to prioritize my work such that I am ahead of schedule, so that I have room for any unexpected changes or upsets in my schedule. \nThings that help me stay on track are my diary/planner, my e-calendar and reminders that I set on my phone for important tasks. For particular projects, I also like to use a Gantt chart, so that I can plan and track particular tasks in the project. \nFor tasks that need to be done with other people, I like to stay on top of things by starting discussions early, so that team members can coordinate their meetings well in advance, instead of delaying tasks until the last moment.",
        "roleQuestion6": "",
        "roleQuestion7": "",
        "roleQuestion8": "",
        "roleQuestion9": "",
        "roleSpecificQuestions": {
            "Project Developer": "I have always been comfortable with coding in Java, C++, Python, etc. However, I struggled with front-end development because I found it slightly monotonous. This proved to be a hindrance when I wanted to build my own website. My only option was to actually sit down and learn how to code with HTML and CSS. Thus, I began doing online courses to familiarize myself with the web-building tools. Even after taking these courses, I could not build my website perfectly. Finally, I began working with friends and mentors on web development side-projects so that I could get actual hands-on experience with front-end development. This is when I actually got the hang of coding in HTML and CSS. I even worked on simple projects of my own in order to test my capabilities.",
            "VP Events": "I like to prioritize my time based on the urgency of the task – I rank my tasks in order of what needs to be completed first and what can be completed subsequently. I also like to prioritize my work such that I am ahead of schedule, so that I have room for any unexpected changes or upsets in my schedule. \nThings that help me stay on track are my diary/planner, my e-calendar and reminders that I set on my phone for important tasks. For particular projects, I also like to use a Gantt chart, so that I can plan and track particular tasks in the project. \nFor tasks that need to be done with other people, I like to stay on top of things by starting discussions early, so that team members can coordinate their meetings well in advance, instead of delaying tasks until the last moment.",
            "VP Projects": "At a science fair organized by my school classmates and I for 1000 students, there was a major issue of task delegation. Students on the organizing team did not come forward to pick particular tasks for themselves; instead, they just tried to help with general tasks. Hence, when issues relating to particular tasks arose, no one took ownership of those issues. I created a chart based on skillset and incomplete tasks, and assigned tasks to each student based on what matched their skills. They were expected to report to their task manager each day with updates, and these updates were added to the chart. The chart was also used to track the expected time for task completion against the time being spent on the task (task progress). Thus, tasks were completed more smoothly."
        },
        "status": "pending",
        "timestamp": 1551868790869
    }
]